<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>economy on Ramon Suarez&#39;s curiosity lead learning life</title>
    <link>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/tags/economy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in economy on Ramon Suarez&#39;s curiosity lead learning life</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2010 17:18:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://test.ramonsuarez.com/tags/economy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Selfmade man in internet communication: interview at 20 Knappe Koppen by @kodel</title>
      <link>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/selfmade-man-in-internet-communication-interv/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2010 17:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/selfmade-man-in-internet-communication-interv/</guid>
      <description>I was lucky enough to be considered one of those internet brains, but I think that what tilted the balance was how I enjoy the good restaurants of Brussels. Nothing beats a nice conversation over lunch like the one we had! The place of choice was Houtsiplou, home of a good selection of quality burgers.
The conversation was mostly in English, but as you can see it has been published in Dutch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Europe&amp;#8217;s Blooming Tech Entrepreneurs</title>
      <link>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/europes-blooming-tech-entrepreneurs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2010 15:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/europes-blooming-tech-entrepreneurs/</guid>
      <description>The two things that struck me the most were:??
The seed and start-up venture capital structure in Europe. The shocking list of the barriers to entrepreneurship index made by the OECD. Italy, Spain and Sweden have lower barriers than the USA. It has also left me thinking about the Venture Capital divide.
Great food for thought.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The future is not Free: a Belgian Android example</title>
      <link>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/the-future-is-not-free-a-belgian-android-exam/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2010 08:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/the-future-is-not-free-a-belgian-android-exam/</guid>
      <description>[Free](http://www.wired.com/techbiz/it/magazine/16-03/ff_free?currentPage=all &amp;ldquo;Chris Anderson&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Free! Why $0.00 Is the Future of Business&amp;rdquo; article in Wired Magazine&amp;rdquo;) is not the Holy Grail of the Internet. To have a sustainable ecosystem we need to have sources of revenue that do not involve having half the planet using our service. Smaller companies tailoring a product to a smaller audience must charge to sustain their business… and that is good!
Free, for most of the companies, is nothing more than an appetizer to their products and services, it is a marketing tool.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Revenge and the unlogical logics of economics</title>
      <link>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/revenge-and-the-unlogical-logics-of-economics/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2009 09:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/revenge-and-the-unlogical-logics-of-economics/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
