<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>devcom on Ramon Suarez&#39;s curiosity lead learning life</title>
    <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/tags/devcom/</link>
    <description>Recent content in devcom on Ramon Suarez&#39;s curiosity lead learning life</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2010 13:25:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ramonsuarez.github.io/tags/devcom/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Search Engine Optimization checklist for DevCom Brussels</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/search-engine-optimization-checklist-for-devc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2010 13:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/search-engine-optimization-checklist-for-devc/</guid>
      <description>Some marketing and communication professionals wrongly despise SEO, considering it just a bunch of technical tricks used to divert Internet users towards sites not worthy of their attention. The truth is that they should look at it from the perspective of their clients: good SEO helps users find the content they are looking for. SEO is not some arkane cult or ritual. Most marketing and communication professionals know some of its basics thanks to their education in journalism, and most of the rest are very easy to imply using a little reasoning and common sense or even better: reading.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Media Conference at DevCom Brussels</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/social-media-conference-at-devcom-brussels/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2010 12:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/social-media-conference-at-devcom-brussels/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Engage your clients using Twitter: Devcom.be demo notes</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/engage-your-clients-using-twitter-devcombe-de/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2010 12:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/engage-your-clients-using-twitter-devcombe-de/</guid>
      <description>Tomorrow I’will be participating in DevCom Brussels, a forum for commercial development in Belgium. Besides networking and getting inspired by the conferences, I will be speaking about social media and also doing 7 minute one to one demos. One of them will be an introduction to Twitter, covering the basic reasons, advantages and things to keep in mind when using it (although these can be applied to all social networks). This are the notes I’ve prepared:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
