<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Ramon Suarez&#39;s curiosity lead learning life</title>
    <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/categories/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Ramon Suarez&#39;s curiosity lead learning life</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2019 09:40:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ramonsuarez.github.io/categories/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>New Project: Sales Acceleration</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/new-project-sales-acceleration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2019 09:40:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/new-project-sales-acceleration/</guid>
      <description>I’ve taken a few weeks off to enjoy the summer break with my family and to think about the challenge. A lot of doubts have assaulted my head and heart, mainly regarding the validity of my approach and what to do next.
If you are reading my emails, you know that I’ve struggled a bit with this. Part of my struggles has to do with a repeating yearly happening: seasonal affective disorder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First 12 Week Year in Review</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/my-first-12-week-year-in-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2019 12:19:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/my-first-12-week-year-in-review/</guid>
      <description>Since the launch of my first 12 week year a lot of things have happened and I’ve been able to continue churning out projects as part of my challenge.
12 Week Year One Results Projects The core of this three month year has been the projects and it has worked well. I’ve worked on other projects too (like the Target Shooting Journal), but the core of the challenge has been kept alive through:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My 12 Week Year Scorecard: Follow My Progress</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/my-12-week-year-scorecard-follow-my-progress-live/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 16:01:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/my-12-week-year-scorecard-follow-my-progress-live/</guid>
      <description>Part of the challenge of having goals and deadlines is tracking them and being able to see your project’s progress. To help me out I’m working on this scorecard that tracks the main goals and tactics of each 12 Week Year.
I’ve scoured the Internet for some templates to use and my scorecard is based on the spreadsheet created by Carrie Dils.
This is what the current scorecard looks like:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Life Goals and the Plan to Implement Them Using the 12 Week Year</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/my-vision-and-plan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2019 15:56:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/my-vision-and-plan/</guid>
      <description>One of the things that I want to improve through practice is structuring my work. Planning every week and day, keeping a productivity journal and using a task manager for all my projects has helped. I have advanced a lot in structuring and I’m now working to take it another step further with the implementation of a long term vision.
An important part of planning is prioritization, and for me this is intimately linked to your vision for the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Project: Shooting Journal</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/new-project-shooting-journal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 16:27:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/new-project-shooting-journal/</guid>
      <description>Since the last time… Last week I spent time going through my business ideation framework and came up with twenty some new ideas easily. I also came up with new questions accelerate the process. The time frame was too short to be able to really work on improving the framework a lot, but at least I improved the spreadsheet to organize the ideas.
So mixed success in last week’s project and now a new challenge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Project: Business Idea Sprint</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/new-project-business-idea-sprint/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 11:28:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/new-project-business-idea-sprint/</guid>
      <description>Come out with new project ideas for the challenge. Improve the framework itself and think about how to best deliver it. My first sprint ended with 145 ideas in the list and I’ve added 21 more since then. I keep them all in a spreadsheet that is very helpful to filter them out by my criteria: Make, Learn, Invest, Drop, and also to mark some as done and remove them from the list of ideas yet to be made.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flop # 3: Coworking Course Post-Mortem</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/fail-3-coworking-course-post-mortem/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 15:54:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/fail-3-coworking-course-post-mortem/</guid>
      <description>After all the ins and outs of this course, only 4 people signed up. This is far from the target of 10 that I committed to in mastermind/accountability group. So I cancelled it, reimbursed everybody and closed my account in the e-learning platform (I don’t know if I will release it again nor when). In fact this puts on hold the other coworking courses I had in mind (marketing and sales).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ins and Outs of the  Coworking Course Launch</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/coworking-course-launched/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 15:19:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/coworking-course-launched/</guid>
      <description>It took a while, but the coworking community course has finally been launched. I kept my timing and the email announcing it went out last Thursday.
Doing a text only course was a good choice. It is much easier to work and rework the content and I can make the delivery much faster. The students have to put their time into doing the tasks to improve their own coworking space community, not on trying to understand my accent in a video.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Morphing: Online Text Course</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/project-morphing-online-text-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2019 12:32:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/project-morphing-online-text-course/</guid>
      <description>I’m not good with video yet, but there are many other delivery methods to share valuable content and help many people. So I’m going to continue working on the Coworking Community Course with a text only course.
The core of the course is ready, I have about 130 slides with a mix of information and exercises. It is a workbook focused on getting coworking space operators to take actions that will help them build a vibrant and healthy communities while they are taking the course and that will give provide a toolbox they can keep on using and referring to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting over Procrastination and Creator&amp;#8217;s Block</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/getting-over-procrastination-and-creators-block/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 15:16:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/getting-over-procrastination-and-creators-block/</guid>
      <description>Two things have contributed to this:
Creator’s block Self confidence Creator’s Block Making and online course is a creator challenge. Even if I’m using the content of my coworking book as the base, I’m adding a lot of content and I’m drafting it for video delivery.
I have a lot of experience writing, but not writing for video. Long gone are my days at Canal + in Spain where I was asked to do some writing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Results of the Email Reactivation &amp;#038; Segmentation  campaign (&gt;11k emails sent)</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/results-of-the-email-reactivation-segmentation-campaign-11k-emails-sent/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 11:09:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/results-of-the-email-reactivation-segmentation-campaign-11k-emails-sent/</guid>
      <description>Super Positive Emails The best thing I’ve gotten out of this email blast are a lot of positive emails from people I have not spoken to in a while. They’ve been motivating and great to catch up with. Some of them have ended up in lunches and meetings that have just been great. I got a lot of love!
One of the most unexpected and motivating emails came from my father in law, Graziano.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fiverr Order Results: Coworking Infographics and Quotes</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/fiverr-order-results-coworking-infographics-and-quotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 11:50:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/fiverr-order-results-coworking-infographics-and-quotes/</guid>
      <description>Finally! It has taken a lot longer than expected, but the orders I submitted to Fiverr have been completed.
The results are… okayish at best. The one I’m unhappiest about is also the one that took more interactions (way too many).
Here are the two info graphics I ordered. Same information on both:
The blue one is too corporate, but it beats the other one by far, although the artist missed the vibe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update: Coworking Courses, Email Segmentation, Meditation Goals</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/update-coworking-courses-email-segmentation-meditation-goals/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 11:38:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/update-coworking-courses-email-segmentation-meditation-goals/</guid>
      <description>Coworking Courses This week I launched a poll to the members of The Coworking Handbook Newsletter asking them for their priorities for a coworking course: sales or community. The answer was a clear both, so I’ve started both of them.
To learn the ropes and get my hand dirtied I’ve chosen to go first with the coworking community course. It is much shorter than the sales course so it will be easier to finish and launch it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Project: Coworking Course</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/new-project-coworking-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 11:58:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/new-project-coworking-course/</guid>
      <description>After two short projects in the challenge, it is time for another monthly undertaking. This time I will be preparing a coworking course that builds on and expands The Coworking Handbook. The book’s content is still 100% valid and applicable, but I can add extra knowledge from running Betacowork the years after I published the book (and from selling it!).
I’ve already spent some time looking into platforms like Udemy, Teachable and Skillshare among others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update: Email Marketing, Repurposing, Outsourcing, Automation</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/update-email-marketing-repurposing-outsourcing-automation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 14:51:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/update-email-marketing-repurposing-outsourcing-automation/</guid>
      <description>Another busy and motivating week has just gone by and things are looking good. Here is this week’s progress report.
As Ash Maurya says:
Practice Trumps Theory
One of the main reasons for the entrepreneurship challenge is to get my hands dirty and it is working wonders.
Revamping Network and Mailing Lists So far 1479 emails of the segmentation project have gone out. The few responses I’m getting are extremely positive and I’ve had my first meeting thanks to it today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Week&amp;#8217;s Focus: Repurposing, Outsourcing, Automation</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/this-weeks-focus-repurposing-outsourcing-automation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 11:23:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/this-weeks-focus-repurposing-outsourcing-automation/</guid>
      <description>After the launch of my email campaign to refresh my network, I ‘ve decided to continue building on my skills and focus on three of the things I want to improve:
Repurposing content. Outsourcing some of my work. Automate as much as possible. Repurposing I have produced a lot of content, be it in the form of blog posts, books, conferences, social media shares… A lot of it is evergreen content (content that is good forever, that does not go bad after a certain date).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dipping My Toes into Email Marketing Automation</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/dipping-my-toes-into-email-marketing-automation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 18:51:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/dipping-my-toes-into-email-marketing-automation/</guid>
      <description>As part of my entrepreneurship challenge, I’m now dipping my toes into email marketing automation to take advantage of all the contacts I’ve collected through the years and try to deliver value to them based on their interests.
So far I’ve imported over 25.000 contacts to Mautic and a few of the imports are still on hold. There will have to be a major cleaning afterwards. I feel a bit like the star of Going Postal, overwhelmed by the amount of mail to deliver.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Results Project #1: Flop</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/results-project-1-flop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 11:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/results-project-1-flop/</guid>
      <description>The launch of coworking.space has been a flop. The first KPI is far from being fulfilled. 18 spaces signed up but almost none of them edited their landing page. The first one that did, completely ignored the guidelines and did not even include a link to their site even after telling them about it. The only coworking space that followed the guidelines was Betacowork, my former coworking space (where I still work 1 to 3 days a week), and with a lot of help from me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meditate Every Day for a Year</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/meditate-every-day-for-a-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 14:06:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/meditate-every-day-for-a-year/</guid>
      <description>Meditation has had a profound positive impact in my life. Being more aware is bringing a lot of improvements to my actions and feelings. It has improved my work, my personal relationships and my sport practice. I enjoy the benefits of awareness/mindfulness meditation.
I started meditating in 2015 with a book and it was okayish, but when I started using the HeadSpace app I really felt the difference. After doing the fist 10 sessions I noticed that something had already changed in me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update on the Launch Of coworking.space</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/update-on-the-launch-of-coworking-space/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 15:27:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/update-on-the-launch-of-coworking-space/</guid>
      <description>Don’t miss any of my adventures as a Jedi entrepreneur
Since the public launch of coworking.space last week (and of my entrepreneurship challenge) I’ve been ramping up the promotion of the service to try to get more spaces in via Facebook groups and pages, reddit, email and some advertising. My post to the coworking Google group is held for moderation.
Sign-ups So far 18 spaces have signed up… but only one has drafted the listing following the guidelines and with help from me: Betacowork Coworking Brussels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Launching at Least One Project Every Month: My Entrepreneurship Learning Challenge</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/launching-at-least-one-project-every-month-my-entrepreneurship-learning-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 18:01:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/launching-at-least-one-project-every-month-my-entrepreneurship-learning-challenge/</guid>
      <description>After the sale of my coworking space I took a few months of vacation to charge up and care for my family. I needed to spend time with myself and to get ready for my next entrepreneurial challenge. There’s no doubt in my mind that my next step is as an entrepreneur: I want to create a business, buy one, or join one as a partner, not get a job.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
