<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>email on Ramon Suarez&#39;s curiosity lead learning life</title>
    <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/tags/email/</link>
    <description>Recent content in email on Ramon Suarez&#39;s curiosity lead learning life</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2011 09:54:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ramonsuarez.github.io/tags/email/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Choosing the Right Channel to Request Attention</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/choosing-the-right-channel-to-request-attenti/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2011 09:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/choosing-the-right-channel-to-request-attenti/</guid>
      <description> The communication channnel choice is complex and does not depend on cost. The more attention it requires, the less people we interact with regularly. The two extremes of the table are Skype video conversations (3) and Facebook/Twitter broadcasting (100+) Cultural impact of availability on the choice of channel: the bussier the other person is, the less we will use a highly synchronous channel like phone or Skype. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why we do not read email marketing messages: too frequent, irrelevant, spammy</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/why-we-do-not-read-email-marketing-messages-t/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2010 13:01:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/why-we-do-not-read-email-marketing-messages-t/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video: The state of the Internet in numbers</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/video-the-state-of-the-internet-in-numbers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2010 16:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/video-the-state-of-the-internet-in-numbers/</guid>
      <description>The numbers have been included with all their zeros (taking into account USA numbering) to make it easier to grasp the volumes we are talking about and to try to avoid some of the mistakes that are usually made when transferring billions and trillions from country to country. It will also be easier to do copy and pasting to a spreadsheet program (which sucks in transnational settings.) I have outlined a couple disparities in numbers, which are probably due to rounding and differences in the dates of samples.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seniors online statistics (US)</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/seniors-online-statistics-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2009 11:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/seniors-online-statistics-us/</guid>
      <description>December 10th, 2009 | by Ben Parr
View comments23 Comments and 719 Reactions
The research confirmed a trend that we’ve seen in recent years: that more seniors are becoming active on the web. In November of 2004, there were 11.3 million active seniors online. In November 2009, that number jumped by 55% to 17.5 million. In addition, they spend more time on the web, totaling an average of 58 hours a month in front of the browser.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
