<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cpartyeu on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/tags/cpartyeu/</link>
    <description>Recent content in cpartyeu on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2010 09:17:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.ramonsuarez.com/tags/cpartyeu/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>European Blogosphere Stats (Campus Party Europe Presentation)</title>
      <link>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/european-blogosphere-stats-campus-party-europ/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2010 09:17:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/european-blogosphere-stats-campus-party-europ/</guid>
      <description>Beyond the great experience of spending a few days in a super-geeky event, I also had the opportunity to prepare with Jonan this study about the perception of the European Blogosphere based on the responses given by European bloggers invited to Campus Party Europe. This is not a scientific work, it is fully subjective but still bears a lot of interesting information that prompted a very interesting debate with my copresenter Ben Hammersley and with the audience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Design Innovation &amp;#038; Future of Internet: Paul Bennet &amp;#038; Ben Hammersley at Campus Party Europe</title>
      <link>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/design-innovation-future-of-internet-paul-ben/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2010 10:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/design-innovation-future-of-internet-paul-ben/</guid>
      <description>The Digital Creativity area of Campus Party Europe could not have had a better start. This morning Paul Bennet and Ben Hammersley have given two very interestin presentations about design innovation and the future of Internet. These are the highlights I have retained:
Paul Bennet “Design Innovation” IDEO’s journey current stage is Framing: design redefines the challenges facing organizations.
Design is about change, impact and optimism.
Now dealing with bigger issues: design of everyday life, social interactions &amp;amp; behaviors, countries and societies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ramon&amp;#8217;s Madrid Top 10 Eating and Drinking Spots</title>
      <link>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/ramons-madrid-top-10-eating-and-drinking-spot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2010 09:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/ramons-madrid-top-10-eating-and-drinking-spot/</guid>
      <description>Here’s the list of my favorite places to eat and drink in Madrid, my much loved hometown. They are all either in the center of the city or within a short bus ride. There are a hell of a lot more good places and you will see that the city is very lively around socializing in bars and restaurants, and above all night life.
If you have time and can read Spanish, I recommend taking a look at the Madrid Tapas’ Guide by Pisto y Nopisto (a refined eating and drinking blog) and this very complete tapas guide.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
