<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Marketing on Ramon Suarez&#39;s curiosity lead learning life</title>
    <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/categories/marketing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Marketing on Ramon Suarez&#39;s curiosity lead learning life</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2019 09:40:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ramonsuarez.github.io/categories/marketing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>New Project: Sales Acceleration</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/new-project-sales-acceleration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2019 09:40:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/new-project-sales-acceleration/</guid>
      <description>I’ve taken a few weeks off to enjoy the summer break with my family and to think about the challenge. A lot of doubts have assaulted my head and heart, mainly regarding the validity of my approach and what to do next.
If you are reading my emails, you know that I’ve struggled a bit with this. Part of my struggles has to do with a repeating yearly happening: seasonal affective disorder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Results of the Email Reactivation &amp;#038; Segmentation  campaign (&gt;11k emails sent)</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/results-of-the-email-reactivation-segmentation-campaign-11k-emails-sent/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 11:09:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/results-of-the-email-reactivation-segmentation-campaign-11k-emails-sent/</guid>
      <description>Super Positive Emails The best thing I’ve gotten out of this email blast are a lot of positive emails from people I have not spoken to in a while. They’ve been motivating and great to catch up with. Some of them have ended up in lunches and meetings that have just been great. I got a lot of love!
One of the most unexpected and motivating emails came from my father in law, Graziano.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fiverr Order Results: Coworking Infographics and Quotes</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/fiverr-order-results-coworking-infographics-and-quotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 11:50:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/fiverr-order-results-coworking-infographics-and-quotes/</guid>
      <description>Finally! It has taken a lot longer than expected, but the orders I submitted to Fiverr have been completed.
The results are… okayish at best. The one I’m unhappiest about is also the one that took more interactions (way too many).
Here are the two info graphics I ordered. Same information on both:
The blue one is too corporate, but it beats the other one by far, although the artist missed the vibe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diving Deep into Online Course Making with Udemy</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/diving-deep-into-online-course-making-with-udemy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 11:30:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/diving-deep-into-online-course-making-with-udemy/</guid>
      <description>This week I’ve been really digging deep into Udemy’s help section for instructors. After finishing the outline for my Coworking Community course last week (I’m still looking for feedback).
I’ve finished all their video courses on how to create your content and how to record it and now I’m trying to get through with their Market Your Course 101 site. I’ve read a lot, and taken a lot of notes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Project: Coworking Course</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/new-project-coworking-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 11:58:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/new-project-coworking-course/</guid>
      <description>After two short projects in the challenge, it is time for another monthly undertaking. This time I will be preparing a coworking course that builds on and expands The Coworking Handbook. The book’s content is still 100% valid and applicable, but I can add extra knowledge from running Betacowork the years after I published the book (and from selling it!).
I’ve already spent some time looking into platforms like Udemy, Teachable and Skillshare among others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update: Email Marketing, Repurposing, Outsourcing, Automation</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/update-email-marketing-repurposing-outsourcing-automation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 14:51:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/update-email-marketing-repurposing-outsourcing-automation/</guid>
      <description>Another busy and motivating week has just gone by and things are looking good. Here is this week’s progress report.
As Ash Maurya says:
Practice Trumps Theory
One of the main reasons for the entrepreneurship challenge is to get my hands dirty and it is working wonders.
Revamping Network and Mailing Lists So far 1479 emails of the segmentation project have gone out. The few responses I’m getting are extremely positive and I’ve had my first meeting thanks to it today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Week&amp;#8217;s Focus: Repurposing, Outsourcing, Automation</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/this-weeks-focus-repurposing-outsourcing-automation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 11:23:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/this-weeks-focus-repurposing-outsourcing-automation/</guid>
      <description>After the launch of my email campaign to refresh my network, I ‘ve decided to continue building on my skills and focus on three of the things I want to improve:
Repurposing content. Outsourcing some of my work. Automate as much as possible. Repurposing I have produced a lot of content, be it in the form of blog posts, books, conferences, social media shares… A lot of it is evergreen content (content that is good forever, that does not go bad after a certain date).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Email Segmentation Campaign Is Rolling!</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/the-email-segmentation-campaign-is-rolling/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 11:37:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/the-email-segmentation-campaign-is-rolling/</guid>
      <description>The email segmentation &amp;amp; reactivation campaign to freshen up my mailing lists is set up and rolling.
Choosing the Right Tool and Cleaning Up Contacts I dropped Mautic for being too complicated and awful to clean up contacts (the main problem I have with all the CRM I’ve tried so far). At the end I went for a much easier set up with the help of a Google add-on by Amit Argawal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dipping My Toes into Email Marketing Automation</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/dipping-my-toes-into-email-marketing-automation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 18:51:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/dipping-my-toes-into-email-marketing-automation/</guid>
      <description>As part of my entrepreneurship challenge, I’m now dipping my toes into email marketing automation to take advantage of all the contacts I’ve collected through the years and try to deliver value to them based on their interests.
So far I’ve imported over 25.000 contacts to Mautic and a few of the imports are still on hold. There will have to be a major cleaning afterwards. I feel a bit like the star of Going Postal, overwhelmed by the amount of mail to deliver.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
