<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Coworking on Ramon Suarez&#39;s curiosity lead learning life</title>
    <link>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/categories/coworking/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Coworking on Ramon Suarez&#39;s curiosity lead learning life</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2019 09:40:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://test.ramonsuarez.com/categories/coworking/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>New Project: Sales Acceleration</title>
      <link>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/new-project-sales-acceleration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2019 09:40:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/new-project-sales-acceleration/</guid>
      <description>I’ve taken a few weeks off to enjoy the summer break with my family and to think about the challenge. A lot of doubts have assaulted my head and heart, mainly regarding the validity of my approach and what to do next.
If you are reading my emails, you know that I’ve struggled a bit with this. Part of my struggles has to do with a repeating yearly happening: seasonal affective disorder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Am I a Solution Looking for a Problem?</title>
      <link>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/am-i-a-solution-looking-for-a-problem/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 12:10:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/am-i-a-solution-looking-for-a-problem/</guid>
      <description>I’m struggling with what to do about my knowledge of coworking and the assets I’ve built about it.
At the same time I cannot help but think that I’m trying too much to develop coworking related projects. There’s this inner struggle between turning the page and forgetting about it, and using these assets to build some side projects and sources of income.
My coworking book is something I’m proud of, that is helping a lot of people, and that is still bringing some revenue every month.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ins and Outs of the  Coworking Course Launch</title>
      <link>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/coworking-course-launched/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 15:19:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/coworking-course-launched/</guid>
      <description>It took a while, but the coworking community course has finally been launched. I kept my timing and the email announcing it went out last Thursday.
Doing a text only course was a good choice. It is much easier to work and rework the content and I can make the delivery much faster. The students have to put their time into doing the tasks to improve their own coworking space community, not on trying to understand my accent in a video.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Morphing: Online Text Course</title>
      <link>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/project-morphing-online-text-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2019 12:32:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/project-morphing-online-text-course/</guid>
      <description>I’m not good with video yet, but there are many other delivery methods to share valuable content and help many people. So I’m going to continue working on the Coworking Community Course with a text only course.
The core of the course is ready, I have about 130 slides with a mix of information and exercises. It is a workbook focused on getting coworking space operators to take actions that will help them build a vibrant and healthy communities while they are taking the course and that will give provide a toolbox they can keep on using and referring to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting over Procrastination and Creator&amp;#8217;s Block</title>
      <link>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/getting-over-procrastination-and-creators-block/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 15:16:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/getting-over-procrastination-and-creators-block/</guid>
      <description>Two things have contributed to this:
Creator’s block Self confidence Creator’s Block Making and online course is a creator challenge. Even if I’m using the content of my coworking book as the base, I’m adding a lot of content and I’m drafting it for video delivery.
I have a lot of experience writing, but not writing for video. Long gone are my days at Canal + in Spain where I was asked to do some writing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update: Coworking Courses, Email Segmentation, Meditation Goals</title>
      <link>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/update-coworking-courses-email-segmentation-meditation-goals/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 11:38:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/update-coworking-courses-email-segmentation-meditation-goals/</guid>
      <description>Coworking Courses This week I launched a poll to the members of The Coworking Handbook Newsletter asking them for their priorities for a coworking course: sales or community. The answer was a clear both, so I’ve started both of them.
To learn the ropes and get my hand dirtied I’ve chosen to go first with the coworking community course. It is much shorter than the sales course so it will be easier to finish and launch it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Project: Coworking Course</title>
      <link>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/new-project-coworking-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 11:58:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/new-project-coworking-course/</guid>
      <description>After two short projects in the challenge, it is time for another monthly undertaking. This time I will be preparing a coworking course that builds on and expands The Coworking Handbook. The book’s content is still 100% valid and applicable, but I can add extra knowledge from running Betacowork the years after I published the book (and from selling it!).
I’ve already spent some time looking into platforms like Udemy, Teachable and Skillshare among others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Results Project #1: Flop</title>
      <link>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/results-project-1-flop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 11:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/results-project-1-flop/</guid>
      <description>The launch of coworking.space has been a flop. The first KPI is far from being fulfilled. 18 spaces signed up but almost none of them edited their landing page. The first one that did, completely ignored the guidelines and did not even include a link to their site even after telling them about it. The only coworking space that followed the guidelines was Betacowork, my former coworking space (where I still work 1 to 3 days a week), and with a lot of help from me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update on the Launch Of coworking.space</title>
      <link>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/update-on-the-launch-of-coworking-space/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 15:27:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/update-on-the-launch-of-coworking-space/</guid>
      <description>Don’t miss any of my adventures as a Jedi entrepreneur
Since the public launch of coworking.space last week (and of my entrepreneurship challenge) I’ve been ramping up the promotion of the service to try to get more spaces in via Facebook groups and pages, reddit, email and some advertising. My post to the coworking Google group is held for moderation.
Sign-ups So far 18 spaces have signed up… but only one has drafted the listing following the guidelines and with help from me: Betacowork Coworking Brussels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Launching at Least One Project Every Month: My Entrepreneurship Learning Challenge</title>
      <link>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/launching-at-least-one-project-every-month-my-entrepreneurship-learning-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 18:01:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/launching-at-least-one-project-every-month-my-entrepreneurship-learning-challenge/</guid>
      <description>After the sale of my coworking space I took a few months of vacation to charge up and care for my family. I needed to spend time with myself and to get ready for my next entrepreneurial challenge. There’s no doubt in my mind that my next step is as an entrepreneur: I want to create a business, buy one, or join one as a partner, not get a job.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
