<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>interview on Ramon Suarez&#39;s curiosity lead learning life</title>
    <link>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/tags/interview/</link>
    <description>Recent content in interview on Ramon Suarez&#39;s curiosity lead learning life</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 May 2013 14:21:21 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://test.ramonsuarez.com/tags/interview/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Mateusz Kukulka et TNW2013: Dynamisme et startups</title>
      <link>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/mateusz-kukulka-et-tnw2013-dynamisme-et-startups/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2013 14:21:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/mateusz-kukulka-et-tnw2013-dynamisme-et-startups/</guid>
      <description>Après une superbe experience au concours de startups à The Next Web Conference 2013, Mateusz Kukulka et moi sommes rentrés à Bruxelles et on a profité pour faire une vidéo de valorisation de son expérience.
Pour ceux qui ne lui connaissent pas encore, Mateusz est un des influencers les plus importants du web et médias sociaux belges, en plus de papa, social media manager, journaliste, coworker, copy, conversationalist, et médiavore.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PeerReach: find and understand social media influencers</title>
      <link>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/peerreach-find-and-understand-social-media-in/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2012 11:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/peerreach-find-and-understand-social-media-in/</guid>
      <description>PeerReach is a tool to find the influencers in a topic, language and geographic area. But it does more than help you find them, it helps you understand their main areas of interest and influence in each one of them.
You probably thought of other tools that are stablished in the market- like Klout, PeerIndex and Kredly- that already do something similar. These competitors are focused on their ranking number and are not so good in defining the right areas of interest and influence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smarter than Siri: Jini, a proactive personal assistant on your smartphone</title>
      <link>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/smarter-than-siri-jini-a-proactive-personal-a/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2012 08:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/smarter-than-siri-jini-a-proactive-personal-a/</guid>
      <description>Jini is an application for smartphones that proactively sugests you things to do based on other applications usage (like RunKeeper) and the sensor information from your phone (location, speed, light…)
Filip Maertens is the founder of this Belgian startup that can really change our mobile world. A good example of what Jini does: when he arrived to Paris to present at the Startup competition at LeWeb, Jini sugested a route to go jogging close to his hotel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Movember in the Belgian TV News (minute 8:20)</title>
      <link>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/movember-in-the-belgian-tv-news-minute-820/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2011 08:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/movember-in-the-belgian-tv-news-minute-820/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Entrepreneurship &amp;#038; Coworking: Interviews by Fred Ooms</title>
      <link>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/entrepreneurship-coworking-interviews-by-fred/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2011 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/entrepreneurship-coworking-interviews-by-fred/</guid>
      <description>Fred Ooms has just finished publishing the interview we had a couple months ago. It was really nice to have some time to talk entrepreneurship with somebody like Fred, alumnus of MBA Solvay like myself, and also working with a university to try to bring part of their research knowledge and patents to market. We just set up a video call and got the interview rolling. Nice, lean and true. In his blog you can find a great selection of entrepreneurship video interviews.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What pushed Jean and Ramon to open the Betagroup Coworking Brussels (Betacowork)</title>
      <link>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/what-pushed-jean-and-ramon-to-open-the-betagr/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2011 13:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/what-pushed-jean-and-ramon-to-open-the-betagr/</guid>
      <description>Thanks Fred!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interviews about MBA Solvay: A Life Changing Experience</title>
      <link>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/interview-about-mba-solvay-a-life-changing-ex/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2011 14:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/interview-about-mba-solvay-a-life-changing-ex/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Geekin&amp;#8217; and eatin&amp;#8217; at the Betagroup Coworking Brussels (AKA Betacowork)</title>
      <link>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/geekin-and-eatin-at-the-betagroup-coworking-b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2011 15:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/geekin-and-eatin-at-the-betagroup-coworking-b/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mission cuisine at the Betagroup Coworking Brussels</title>
      <link>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/mission-cuisine-at-the-betagroup-coworking-br/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2011 11:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/mission-cuisine-at-the-betagroup-coworking-br/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Presentation de Startup Weekend Bruxelles</title>
      <link>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/presentation-de-startup-weekend-bruxelles/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2011 20:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/presentation-de-startup-weekend-bruxelles/</guid>
      <description>Video interview by Gérald Trockart.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>xpats Portraits: Ramon Suarez (The Bulletin)</title>
      <link>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/xpats-portraits-ramon-suarez-the-bulletin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2011 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/xpats-portraits-ramon-suarez-the-bulletin/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talking about the Betagroup Coworking Brussels: Teknophile  Podcast (RTL)</title>
      <link>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/talking-about-the-betagroup-coworking-brussel/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2011 18:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/talking-about-the-betagroup-coworking-brussel/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daniel Santos about LeWeb10</title>
      <link>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/35804765/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2010 09:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/35804765/</guid>
      <description>Daniel Santos, MBA Solvay student and project manager at Toyota in Brussels, tells us about his LeWeb10 expectations: the startups &amp;amp; people to meet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Renault to Rent the Batteries of Its New Electric Cars</title>
      <link>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/renault-to-rent-the-batteries-of-its-new-elec/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2010 08:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/renault-to-rent-the-batteries-of-its-new-elec/</guid>
      <description>Renault is bringing an interesting business model to the market with its new electric cars: they will sell the cars and rent the batteries. Advantages for the users: no worries about lifetime of the batteries, recycling taken care of by the company. Advantage for the company: recurring revenue and stronger bond with clients.
Matthieu Tenenbaum, deputy electric car program director, presents the new electric cars (Twizy, Fluence and Dezire), and talks about the business model and partnerships with cities and corporations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lo??c Le Meur &amp;#038; LeWeb10 (interview)</title>
      <link>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/loic-le-meur-leweb10-interview/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2010 10:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/loic-le-meur-leweb10-interview/</guid>
      <description>These are the responses given by Loïc to the short questionnary I sent him. He was really quick tp answer!
What is LeWeb like for Loïc Le Meur? LeWeb is a tool box for the european entpreneur: from the inspiration to find ideas to start a business to networking with Google, Microsoft or Facebook and raising angel or VC money. They can do it all during two days. This year we even have a “how to get acquired” panel to help them understand how to sell their business if they like.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Entrevista: Julio Alonso, LeWeb y el futuro (Loogic.com)</title>
      <link>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/entrevista-julio-alonso-leweb-y-el-futuro-loo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2010 16:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/entrevista-julio-alonso-leweb-y-el-futuro-loo/</guid>
      <description>In this interview we discussed his coming participation in LeWeb10 and also his ideas about the future of Media and the Internet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Selfmade man in internet communication: interview at 20 Knappe Koppen by @kodel</title>
      <link>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/selfmade-man-in-internet-communication-interv/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2010 17:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/selfmade-man-in-internet-communication-interv/</guid>
      <description>I was lucky enough to be considered one of those internet brains, but I think that what tilted the balance was how I enjoy the good restaurants of Brussels. Nothing beats a nice conversation over lunch like the one we had! The place of choice was Houtsiplou, home of a good selection of quality burgers.
The conversation was mostly in English, but as you can see it has been published in Dutch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interview on Le Podcast High-Tech</title>
      <link>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/interview-on-le-podcast-high-tech/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2010 07:20:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/interview-on-le-podcast-high-tech/</guid>
      <description>The interview is in French.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
