<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>tuzzit on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/tags/tuzzit/</link>
    <description>Recent content in tuzzit on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2012 16:16:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.ramonsuarez.com/tags/tuzzit/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>TUZZit: the CheckThis of online project management</title>
      <link>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/tuzzit-the-checkthis-of-online-project-manage/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2012 16:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/tuzzit-the-checkthis-of-online-project-manage/</guid>
      <description>TUZZit is a very promising online project management tool that focuses in ease of use and visual appeal. There are no save buttons and it allows to present ideas and task just like we would do in a whiteboard, with a visual organization instead of a date or alphabet based presentation.
When Christophe Fruyter showed it to me at the Belgian Startups stand at LeWeb, I inmediately thought of CheckThis, the online tool to publish your internet posters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Belgian Startups at #LeWeb12 (aka #beleweb)</title>
      <link>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/belgian-startups-at-leweb12-aka-beleweb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2012 09:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/belgian-startups-at-leweb12-aka-beleweb/</guid>
      <description>For the second year on a row there will be a unified Belgian startups stand at LeWeb. On this occassion there will be 15 startups participating from the three Belgian regions: 14 as part of the Startups.be #beleweb delegation and one in the startup competition (Jini). I will also be there as an official blogger, writing mostly for the Spanish internet business blog Loogic.
87seconds 8thColor Carambla CleverPhone EarlyTracks Freedelity Jini MyMicroInvest Small Town Heroes TagTagCity Tuzzit Twipe Mobile Uniwan WeePee </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
