<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Entrepreneurship on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/categories/Entrepreneurship/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Entrepreneurship on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 08:41:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.ramonsuarez.com/categories/Entrepreneurship/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Traction (EOS) Book Summary and Review</title>
      <link>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/traction-eos-book-summary-and-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 08:41:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/traction-eos-book-summary-and-review/</guid>
      <description>I’ve had to remove all pictures publicly available in other sites, even the promotional picture of the author used in his Amazon profile.
I’ve had to update the capitalization of words to match their style guides, although I do not work for them.
I’ve had to add copyright and trademark symbols all over the place although they are not even mandatory to use and, the TM are not registered (they are just claiming them) and many of them will never be able to be registered because they are just common words being used in a common sense.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Life Goals and the Plan to Implement Them Using the 12 Week Year</title>
      <link>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/my-vision-and-plan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2019 15:56:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/my-vision-and-plan/</guid>
      <description>One of the things that I want to improve through practice is structuring my work. Planning every week and day, keeping a productivity journal and using a task manager for all my projects has helped. I have advanced a lot in structuring and I’m now working to take it another step further with the implementation of a long term vision.
An important part of planning is prioritization, and for me this is intimately linked to your vision for the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Mission Statement For a Company of One</title>
      <link>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/a-mission-statement-for-a-company-of-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2019 11:40:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/a-mission-statement-for-a-company-of-one/</guid>
      <description>One of the things that I have to improve to get my projects off the ground is project management. Among the books I’ve been reading, one has really hit home: Radical Focus: Achieving Your Most Important Goals with Objectives and Key Results.
The title is self explanatory. To work with your OKR (Objectives and Key Results) they recommend having a mission statement for the company to guide you.
My experience with the Mission, Vision and Values of Betacowork was very positive and helpful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dipping My Toes into Email Marketing Automation</title>
      <link>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/dipping-my-toes-into-email-marketing-automation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 18:51:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/dipping-my-toes-into-email-marketing-automation/</guid>
      <description>As part of my entrepreneurship challenge, I’m now dipping my toes into email marketing automation to take advantage of all the contacts I’ve collected through the years and try to deliver value to them based on their interests.
So far I’ve imported over 25.000 contacts to Mautic and a few of the imports are still on hold. There will have to be a major cleaning afterwards. I feel a bit like the star of Going Postal, overwhelmed by the amount of mail to deliver.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Results Project #1: Flop</title>
      <link>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/results-project-1-flop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 11:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/results-project-1-flop/</guid>
      <description>The launch of coworking.space has been a flop. The first KPI is far from being fulfilled. 18 spaces signed up but almost none of them edited their landing page. The first one that did, completely ignored the guidelines and did not even include a link to their site even after telling them about it. The only coworking space that followed the guidelines was Betacowork, my former coworking space (where I still work 1 to 3 days a week), and with a lot of help from me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Launching at Least One Project Every Month: My Entrepreneurship Learning Challenge</title>
      <link>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/launching-at-least-one-project-every-month-my-entrepreneurship-learning-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Oct 2018 18:01:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/launching-at-least-one-project-every-month-my-entrepreneurship-learning-challenge/</guid>
      <description>After the sale of my coworking space I took a few months of vacation to charge up and care for my family. I needed to spend time with myself and to get ready for my next entrepreneurial challenge. There’s no doubt in my mind that my next step is as an entrepreneur: I want to create a business, buy one, or join one as a partner, not get a job.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
