<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>repurposing on Ramon Suarez&#39;s curiosity lead learning life</title>
    <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/tags/repurposing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in repurposing on Ramon Suarez&#39;s curiosity lead learning life</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 14:51:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ramonsuarez.github.io/tags/repurposing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Update: Email Marketing, Repurposing, Outsourcing, Automation</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/update-email-marketing-repurposing-outsourcing-automation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 14:51:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/update-email-marketing-repurposing-outsourcing-automation/</guid>
      <description>Another busy and motivating week has just gone by and things are looking good. Here is this week’s progress report.
As Ash Maurya says:
Practice Trumps Theory
One of the main reasons for the entrepreneurship challenge is to get my hands dirty and it is working wonders.
Revamping Network and Mailing Lists So far 1479 emails of the segmentation project have gone out. The few responses I’m getting are extremely positive and I’ve had my first meeting thanks to it today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Week&amp;#8217;s Focus: Repurposing, Outsourcing, Automation</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/this-weeks-focus-repurposing-outsourcing-automation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 11:23:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/this-weeks-focus-repurposing-outsourcing-automation/</guid>
      <description>After the launch of my email campaign to refresh my network, I ‘ve decided to continue building on my skills and focus on three of the things I want to improve:
Repurposing content. Outsourcing some of my work. Automate as much as possible. Repurposing I have produced a lot of content, be it in the form of blog posts, books, conferences, social media shares… A lot of it is evergreen content (content that is good forever, that does not go bad after a certain date).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
