<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>meditation on Ramon Suarez&#39;s curiosity lead learning life</title>
    <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/tags/meditation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in meditation on Ramon Suarez&#39;s curiosity lead learning life</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 12:17:27 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ramonsuarez.github.io/tags/meditation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Why I&amp;#8217;m Dropping My Daily Meditation Challenge After 7 Months of Daily Practice</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/why-im-dropping-my-daily-meditation-challenge-after-7-months-of-daily-practice/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 12:17:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/why-im-dropping-my-daily-meditation-challenge-after-7-months-of-daily-practice/</guid>
      <description>TL;DR: Because it does not matter.
After 227 days (almost seven and a half months) of daily meditation I missed one day, which broke the challenge I had set up for myself of meditating everyday for a year. The people at Headspace kindly reset the counter so that the streak would not be broken when I asked them how many days I had meditated in a row, but this did not change the fact that I had missed a day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meditated for 100 Days</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/meditated-for-100-days/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2018 16:15:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/meditated-for-100-days/</guid>
      <description>Not a habit yet Although I’ve managed to do so many days of continuous meditation practice it is not yet a habit (and I really wish it was). The 21 days rule is not working for me at all.
Not being able to do it every day at the same time because of the ever changing schedule of parenting makes it really hard to stick and adds a bit of angst, of fear of missing a day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update: Coworking Courses, Email Segmentation, Meditation Goals</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/update-coworking-courses-email-segmentation-meditation-goals/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 11:38:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/update-coworking-courses-email-segmentation-meditation-goals/</guid>
      <description>Coworking Courses This week I launched a poll to the members of The Coworking Handbook Newsletter asking them for their priorities for a coworking course: sales or community. The answer was a clear both, so I’ve started both of them.
To learn the ropes and get my hand dirtied I’ve chosen to go first with the coworking community course. It is much shorter than the sales course so it will be easier to finish and launch it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meditate Every Day for a Year</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/meditate-every-day-for-a-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 14:06:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/meditate-every-day-for-a-year/</guid>
      <description>Meditation has had a profound positive impact in my life. Being more aware is bringing a lot of improvements to my actions and feelings. It has improved my work, my personal relationships and my sport practice. I enjoy the benefits of awareness/mindfulness meditation.
I started meditating in 2015 with a book and it was okayish, but when I started using the HeadSpace app I really felt the difference. After doing the fist 10 sessions I noticed that something had already changed in me.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
