<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>udemy on Ramon Suarez&#39;s curiosity lead learning life</title>
    <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/tags/udemy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in udemy on Ramon Suarez&#39;s curiosity lead learning life</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 14:55:54 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ramonsuarez.github.io/tags/udemy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Flop #2: Deadlines and Video</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/fail-2-deadlines-and-video/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 14:55:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/fail-2-deadlines-and-video/</guid>
      <description>Deadlines need to be precise My first mistake when I launched the video course project was not to set a precise deadline. One month from now is not good enough, I need to have a date and time and keep it visible. I can then also prepare a timeline of the project and evaluate my progress towards it in chunks not just for the completion of the whole course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diving Deep into Online Course Making with Udemy</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/diving-deep-into-online-course-making-with-udemy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 11:30:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/diving-deep-into-online-course-making-with-udemy/</guid>
      <description>This week I’ve been really digging deep into Udemy’s help section for instructors. After finishing the outline for my Coworking Community course last week (I’m still looking for feedback).
I’ve finished all their video courses on how to create your content and how to record it and now I’m trying to get through with their Market Your Course 101 site. I’ve read a lot, and taken a lot of notes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update: Coworking Courses, Email Segmentation, Meditation Goals</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/update-coworking-courses-email-segmentation-meditation-goals/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 11:38:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/update-coworking-courses-email-segmentation-meditation-goals/</guid>
      <description>Coworking Courses This week I launched a poll to the members of The Coworking Handbook Newsletter asking them for their priorities for a coworking course: sales or community. The answer was a clear both, so I’ve started both of them.
To learn the ropes and get my hand dirtied I’ve chosen to go first with the coworking community course. It is much shorter than the sales course so it will be easier to finish and launch it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Project: Coworking Course</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/new-project-coworking-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2018 11:58:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/new-project-coworking-course/</guid>
      <description>After two short projects in the challenge, it is time for another monthly undertaking. This time I will be preparing a coworking course that builds on and expands The Coworking Handbook. The book’s content is still 100% valid and applicable, but I can add extra knowledge from running Betacowork the years after I published the book (and from selling it!).
I’ve already spent some time looking into platforms like Udemy, Teachable and Skillshare among others.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
