<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ideas on Ramon Suarez&#39;s curiosity lead learning life</title>
    <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/tags/ideas/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ideas on Ramon Suarez&#39;s curiosity lead learning life</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2010 08:25:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ramonsuarez.github.io/tags/ideas/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The future is not Free: a Belgian Android example</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/the-future-is-not-free-a-belgian-android-exam/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2010 08:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/the-future-is-not-free-a-belgian-android-exam/</guid>
      <description>[Free](http://www.wired.com/techbiz/it/magazine/16-03/ff_free?currentPage=all &amp;ldquo;Chris Anderson&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Free! Why $0.00 Is the Future of Business&amp;rdquo; article in Wired Magazine&amp;rdquo;) is not the Holy Grail of the Internet. To have a sustainable ecosystem we need to have sources of revenue that do not involve having half the planet using our service. Smaller companies tailoring a product to a smaller audience must charge to sustain their business… and that is good!
Free, for most of the companies, is nothing more than an appetizer to their products and services, it is a marketing tool.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yes, blogging has peaked and it is not a problem</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/yes-blogging-has-peaked-and-it-is-not-a-probl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2010 08:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/yes-blogging-has-peaked-and-it-is-not-a-probl/</guid>
      <description>Of all the blogs I follow, only the professional ones keep up the pace. A lot of personal bloggers have stopped writing or greatly reduced their contributions. Why wouldn’t they with Facebook and Twitter’s instant gratification and reduced effort? Why on earth would we have to consider that it is a problem?
Lets face it, most of the personal blogposts are exactly that, personal, and directed to a group of friends: they will be much better served in a less publicly scrutinized platform like Facebook, or Netlog, or Tuenti, or you-name-the-closed-garden-social-network.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Suggested reading: Manifesto on management 2.0</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/suggested-reading-manifesto-on-management-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2010 09:57:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/suggested-reading-manifesto-on-management-20/</guid>
      <description>Although I agree that the quality of the product is very important, I do not agree with the idea that the product itself is the marketing. This falls into the traditional engineer trap where the creators of a product just concentrate their efforts in the product and disregard marketing.
Without marketing your great product will die in obscurity. There are many forms of marketing and different actions to take depending on your willingness and resources.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
