<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>jini on Ramon Suarez&#39;s curiosity lead learning life</title>
    <link>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/tags/jini/</link>
    <description>Recent content in jini on Ramon Suarez&#39;s curiosity lead learning life</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2012 08:39:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://test.ramonsuarez.com/tags/jini/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Smarter than Siri: Jini, a proactive personal assistant on your smartphone</title>
      <link>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/smarter-than-siri-jini-a-proactive-personal-a/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2012 08:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/smarter-than-siri-jini-a-proactive-personal-a/</guid>
      <description>Jini is an application for smartphones that proactively sugests you things to do based on other applications usage (like RunKeeper) and the sensor information from your phone (location, speed, light…)
Filip Maertens is the founder of this Belgian startup that can really change our mobile world. A good example of what Jini does: when he arrived to Paris to present at the Startup competition at LeWeb, Jini sugested a route to go jogging close to his hotel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Belgian Startups at #LeWeb12 (aka #beleweb)</title>
      <link>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/belgian-startups-at-leweb12-aka-beleweb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2012 09:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/belgian-startups-at-leweb12-aka-beleweb/</guid>
      <description>For the second year on a row there will be a unified Belgian startups stand at LeWeb. On this occassion there will be 15 startups participating from the three Belgian regions: 14 as part of the Startups.be #beleweb delegation and one in the startup competition (Jini). I will also be there as an official blogger, writing mostly for the Spanish internet business blog Loogic.
87seconds 8thColor Carambla CleverPhone EarlyTracks Freedelity Jini MyMicroInvest Small Town Heroes TagTagCity Tuzzit Twipe Mobile Uniwan WeePee </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
