<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>eatanddrink on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/tags/eatanddrink/</link>
    <description>Recent content in eatanddrink on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2011 15:53:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.ramonsuarez.com/tags/eatanddrink/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Geekin&amp;#8217; and eatin&amp;#8217; at the Betagroup Coworking Brussels (AKA Betacowork)</title>
      <link>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/geekin-and-eatin-at-the-betagroup-coworking-b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2011 15:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/geekin-and-eatin-at-the-betagroup-coworking-b/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Selfmade man in internet communication: interview at 20 Knappe Koppen by @kodel</title>
      <link>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/selfmade-man-in-internet-communication-interv/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2010 17:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/selfmade-man-in-internet-communication-interv/</guid>
      <description>I was lucky enough to be considered one of those internet brains, but I think that what tilted the balance was how I enjoy the good restaurants of Brussels. Nothing beats a nice conversation over lunch like the one we had! The place of choice was Houtsiplou, home of a good selection of quality burgers.
The conversation was mostly in English, but as you can see it has been published in Dutch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ramon&amp;#8217;s Madrid Top 10 Eating and Drinking Spots</title>
      <link>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/ramons-madrid-top-10-eating-and-drinking-spot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2010 09:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/ramons-madrid-top-10-eating-and-drinking-spot/</guid>
      <description>Here’s the list of my favorite places to eat and drink in Madrid, my much loved hometown. They are all either in the center of the city or within a short bus ride. There are a hell of a lot more good places and you will see that the city is very lively around socializing in bars and restaurants, and above all night life.
If you have time and can read Spanish, I recommend taking a look at the Madrid Tapas’ Guide by Pisto y Nopisto (a refined eating and drinking blog) and this very complete tapas guide.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
