<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Progress Report on Ramon Suarez&#39;s curiosity lead learning life</title>
    <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/categories/progress-report/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Progress Report on Ramon Suarez&#39;s curiosity lead learning life</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2019 13:14:51 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ramonsuarez.github.io/categories/progress-report/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Flop: Sales Acceleration</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/flop-sales-acceleration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2019 13:14:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/flop-sales-acceleration/</guid>
      <description>The sales acceleration project has been a real flop.
BIGF Method My biggest effort was on the BIGF Method and it did not really pay much: one extra paying customer and only 26 free customers.
I reached out to my contacts, got a post about my ideation method published in Spain, run ads on Quora and Google…
There are a few factors to consider for this flop:
The original landing page that I contracted via Fiverr did not work at all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First 12 Week Year in Review</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/my-first-12-week-year-in-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2019 12:19:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/my-first-12-week-year-in-review/</guid>
      <description>Since the launch of my first 12 week year a lot of things have happened and I’ve been able to continue churning out projects as part of my challenge.
12 Week Year One Results Projects The core of this three month year has been the projects and it has worked well. I’ve worked on other projects too (like the Target Shooting Journal), but the core of the challenge has been kept alive through:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I&amp;#8217;m Dropping My Daily Meditation Challenge After 7 Months of Daily Practice</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/why-im-dropping-my-daily-meditation-challenge-after-7-months-of-daily-practice/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 12:17:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/why-im-dropping-my-daily-meditation-challenge-after-7-months-of-daily-practice/</guid>
      <description>TL;DR: Because it does not matter.
After 227 days (almost seven and a half months) of daily meditation I missed one day, which broke the challenge I had set up for myself of meditating everyday for a year. The people at Headspace kindly reset the counter so that the streak would not be broken when I asked them how many days I had meditated in a row, but this did not change the fact that I had missed a day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My 12 Week Year Scorecard: Follow My Progress</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/my-12-week-year-scorecard-follow-my-progress-live/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 16:01:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/my-12-week-year-scorecard-follow-my-progress-live/</guid>
      <description>Part of the challenge of having goals and deadlines is tracking them and being able to see your project’s progress. To help me out I’m working on this scorecard that tracks the main goals and tactics of each 12 Week Year.
I’ve scoured the Internet for some templates to use and my scorecard is based on the spreadsheet created by Carrie Dils.
This is what the current scorecard looks like:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flop # 3: Coworking Course Post-Mortem</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/fail-3-coworking-course-post-mortem/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 15:54:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/fail-3-coworking-course-post-mortem/</guid>
      <description>After all the ins and outs of this course, only 4 people signed up. This is far from the target of 10 that I committed to in mastermind/accountability group. So I cancelled it, reimbursed everybody and closed my account in the e-learning platform (I don’t know if I will release it again nor when). In fact this puts on hold the other coworking courses I had in mind (marketing and sales).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ins and Outs of the  Coworking Course Launch</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/coworking-course-launched/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 15:19:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/coworking-course-launched/</guid>
      <description>It took a while, but the coworking community course has finally been launched. I kept my timing and the email announcing it went out last Thursday.
Doing a text only course was a good choice. It is much easier to work and rework the content and I can make the delivery much faster. The students have to put their time into doing the tasks to improve their own coworking space community, not on trying to understand my accent in a video.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meditated for 100 Days</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/meditated-for-100-days/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2018 16:15:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/meditated-for-100-days/</guid>
      <description>Not a habit yet Although I’ve managed to do so many days of continuous meditation practice it is not yet a habit (and I really wish it was). The 21 days rule is not working for me at all.
Not being able to do it every day at the same time because of the ever changing schedule of parenting makes it really hard to stick and adds a bit of angst, of fear of missing a day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting over Procrastination and Creator&amp;#8217;s Block</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/getting-over-procrastination-and-creators-block/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 15:16:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/getting-over-procrastination-and-creators-block/</guid>
      <description>Two things have contributed to this:
Creator’s block Self confidence Creator’s Block Making and online course is a creator challenge. Even if I’m using the content of my coworking book as the base, I’m adding a lot of content and I’m drafting it for video delivery.
I have a lot of experience writing, but not writing for video. Long gone are my days at Canal + in Spain where I was asked to do some writing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Results of the Email Reactivation &amp;#038; Segmentation  campaign (&gt;11k emails sent)</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/results-of-the-email-reactivation-segmentation-campaign-11k-emails-sent/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 11:09:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/results-of-the-email-reactivation-segmentation-campaign-11k-emails-sent/</guid>
      <description>Super Positive Emails The best thing I’ve gotten out of this email blast are a lot of positive emails from people I have not spoken to in a while. They’ve been motivating and great to catch up with. Some of them have ended up in lunches and meetings that have just been great. I got a lot of love!
One of the most unexpected and motivating emails came from my father in law, Graziano.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fiverr Order Results: Coworking Infographics and Quotes</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/fiverr-order-results-coworking-infographics-and-quotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Nov 2018 11:50:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/fiverr-order-results-coworking-infographics-and-quotes/</guid>
      <description>Finally! It has taken a lot longer than expected, but the orders I submitted to Fiverr have been completed.
The results are… okayish at best. The one I’m unhappiest about is also the one that took more interactions (way too many).
Here are the two info graphics I ordered. Same information on both:
The blue one is too corporate, but it beats the other one by far, although the artist missed the vibe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diving Deep into Online Course Making with Udemy</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/diving-deep-into-online-course-making-with-udemy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 11:30:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/diving-deep-into-online-course-making-with-udemy/</guid>
      <description>This week I’ve been really digging deep into Udemy’s help section for instructors. After finishing the outline for my Coworking Community course last week (I’m still looking for feedback).
I’ve finished all their video courses on how to create your content and how to record it and now I’m trying to get through with their Market Your Course 101 site. I’ve read a lot, and taken a lot of notes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update: Coworking Courses, Email Segmentation, Meditation Goals</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/update-coworking-courses-email-segmentation-meditation-goals/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 11:38:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/update-coworking-courses-email-segmentation-meditation-goals/</guid>
      <description>Coworking Courses This week I launched a poll to the members of The Coworking Handbook Newsletter asking them for their priorities for a coworking course: sales or community. The answer was a clear both, so I’ve started both of them.
To learn the ropes and get my hand dirtied I’ve chosen to go first with the coworking community course. It is much shorter than the sales course so it will be easier to finish and launch it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update: Email Marketing, Repurposing, Outsourcing, Automation</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/update-email-marketing-repurposing-outsourcing-automation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 14:51:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/update-email-marketing-repurposing-outsourcing-automation/</guid>
      <description>Another busy and motivating week has just gone by and things are looking good. Here is this week’s progress report.
As Ash Maurya says:
Practice Trumps Theory
One of the main reasons for the entrepreneurship challenge is to get my hands dirty and it is working wonders.
Revamping Network and Mailing Lists So far 1479 emails of the segmentation project have gone out. The few responses I’m getting are extremely positive and I’ve had my first meeting thanks to it today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Email Segmentation Campaign Is Rolling!</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/the-email-segmentation-campaign-is-rolling/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 11:37:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/the-email-segmentation-campaign-is-rolling/</guid>
      <description>The email segmentation &amp;amp; reactivation campaign to freshen up my mailing lists is set up and rolling.
Choosing the Right Tool and Cleaning Up Contacts I dropped Mautic for being too complicated and awful to clean up contacts (the main problem I have with all the CRM I’ve tried so far). At the end I went for a much easier set up with the help of a Google add-on by Amit Argawal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Results Project #1: Flop</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/results-project-1-flop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 11:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/results-project-1-flop/</guid>
      <description>The launch of coworking.space has been a flop. The first KPI is far from being fulfilled. 18 spaces signed up but almost none of them edited their landing page. The first one that did, completely ignored the guidelines and did not even include a link to their site even after telling them about it. The only coworking space that followed the guidelines was Betacowork, my former coworking space (where I still work 1 to 3 days a week), and with a lot of help from me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meditate Every Day for a Year</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/meditate-every-day-for-a-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 14:06:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/meditate-every-day-for-a-year/</guid>
      <description>Meditation has had a profound positive impact in my life. Being more aware is bringing a lot of improvements to my actions and feelings. It has improved my work, my personal relationships and my sport practice. I enjoy the benefits of awareness/mindfulness meditation.
I started meditating in 2015 with a book and it was okayish, but when I started using the HeadSpace app I really felt the difference. After doing the fist 10 sessions I noticed that something had already changed in me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update on the Launch Of coworking.space</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/update-on-the-launch-of-coworking-space/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 15:27:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/update-on-the-launch-of-coworking-space/</guid>
      <description>Don’t miss any of my adventures as a Jedi entrepreneur
Since the public launch of coworking.space last week (and of my entrepreneurship challenge) I’ve been ramping up the promotion of the service to try to get more spaces in via Facebook groups and pages, reddit, email and some advertising. My post to the coworking Google group is held for moderation.
Sign-ups So far 18 spaces have signed up… but only one has drafted the listing following the guidelines and with help from me: Betacowork Coworking Brussels.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
