<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>mobile on Ramon Suarez&#39;s curiosity lead learning life</title>
    <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/tags/mobile/</link>
    <description>Recent content in mobile on Ramon Suarez&#39;s curiosity lead learning life</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2012 09:45:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ramonsuarez.github.io/tags/mobile/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Be-Bound: surf the internet without WiFi or data connectivity</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/be-bound-surf-the-internet-without-wifi-or-da/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2012 09:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/be-bound-surf-the-internet-without-wifi-or-da/</guid>
      <description>Be-Bound is the great world changer of the startup competition at LeWeb. They propose a smarphone app that relies on the standard mobile phone networks to allow for Internet use. How do they do it? By sending sms to and from their servers.
To use it you buy prepaid credit and every action (reading an email, forwarding a message, updating your Twitter timeline), costs from one to three credits.
This application can really be useful on areas with no data coverage and for people traveling to other countries that don’t want to pay the hefty roaming data fees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mobile Use in the UK &amp;#038; Germany Infographic</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/mobile-use-in-the-uk-germany-infographic/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2011 08:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/mobile-use-in-the-uk-germany-infographic/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guest post in Alt1040: Fabricantes de dispositivos Android: dejen de joder la interfaz de usuario (carta abierta)</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/guest-post-in-alt1040-fabricantes-de-disposit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2010 17:05:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/guest-post-in-alt1040-fabricantes-de-disposit/</guid>
      <description>As you could imagine, I am honored and happy. It feels like when you get your thoughts published in the letters to the editor section of traditional newspaper: really good. I’m looking forward to the coments by the readers</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android handset manufacturers: stop screwing up the interface (open letter)</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/android-handset-manufacturers-stop-screwing-u/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2010 07:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/android-handset-manufacturers-stop-screwing-u/</guid>
      <description>Dear Android handset manufacturers:??
I understand that you would like to lock-in your users with something more than the hardware you produce, which risks being completely commoditized soon. But please, do yourself and your users a favor and stop screwing up the interface of Android. The user experience with Android needs a lot of refinement still and you are only subtracting from it.??
If you really want to keep a healthy business and prevail over other systems like Apple’s iPhone, what you should do is create an umbrella organization together with Google to help each other produce the best Android interface on earth that will work with all the different devices you make.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why are there so many free Android and iPhone mobile apps?</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/why-are-there-so-many-free-android-and-iphone/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2010 10:01:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/why-are-there-so-many-free-android-and-iphone/</guid>
      <description>Because it is much easier to make an app than to sell an app.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ramon&amp;#8217;s Vision about the Future of Mobile. Keynote Presentation at Droidcon Belgium 2010</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/ramons-vision-about-the-future-of-mobile-keyn/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2010 14:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/ramons-vision-about-the-future-of-mobile-keyn/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dos startups espa??olas en Plugg: art??culo en Loogic.com</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/dos-startups-espanolas-en-plugg-articulo-en-l/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2010 10:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/dos-startups-espanolas-en-plugg-articulo-en-l/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
