<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>tools on Ramon Suarez&#39;s curiosity lead learning life</title>
    <link>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/tags/tools/</link>
    <description>Recent content in tools on Ramon Suarez&#39;s curiosity lead learning life</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2012 11:21:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://test.ramonsuarez.com/tags/tools/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>PeerReach: find and understand social media influencers</title>
      <link>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/peerreach-find-and-understand-social-media-in/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2012 11:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/peerreach-find-and-understand-social-media-in/</guid>
      <description>PeerReach is a tool to find the influencers in a topic, language and geographic area. But it does more than help you find them, it helps you understand their main areas of interest and influence in each one of them.
You probably thought of other tools that are stablished in the market- like Klout, PeerIndex and Kredly- that already do something similar. These competitors are focused on their ranking number and are not so good in defining the right areas of interest and influence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TUZZit: the CheckThis of online project management</title>
      <link>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/tuzzit-the-checkthis-of-online-project-manage/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2012 16:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/tuzzit-the-checkthis-of-online-project-manage/</guid>
      <description>TUZZit is a very promising online project management tool that focuses in ease of use and visual appeal. There are no save buttons and it allows to present ideas and task just like we would do in a whiteboard, with a visual organization instead of a date or alphabet based presentation.
When Christophe Fruyter showed it to me at the Belgian Startups stand at LeWeb, I inmediately thought of CheckThis, the online tool to publish your internet posters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dropbox tips</title>
      <link>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/dropbox-tips/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2011 18:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/dropbox-tips/</guid>
      <description>If you’re like us, you’re using Dropbox for all kinds of unusual tasks. But we wanted to go further, so we asked the experts at Dropbox to tell us their most unusual, unexpected and crazy ways to use this versatile software tool.
If you’re not familiar with Dropbox, it’s free desktop synchronization software that lets you store a copy of a file on your computer and then access that same file from anywhere.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sync video presentations with slides (Omnisio alternatives)</title>
      <link>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/sync-video-presentations-with-slides-omnisio/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Nov 2010 14:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/sync-video-presentations-with-slides-omnisio/</guid>
      <description> There are several alternatives to omnisio:
Use an online tool like Vcasmo or Zentation. Convert the presentation to images and then insert it in the video with a non-linear video editor (I use KDEnlive, here you have a manual for **Microsoft Produce**r). This can be complicated, but it offers more control. Check this video tutorials to learn the basics. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google&amp;#8217;s Site Management Guidelines</title>
      <link>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/googles-site-management-guidelines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2009 11:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/googles-site-management-guidelines/</guid>
      <description>Easy and brief information that will help you be more relevant and findable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google SEM/SEO/SEA tools links</title>
      <link>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/google-semseosea-tools-links/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2009 15:06:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/google-semseosea-tools-links/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
