<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>books on Ramon Suarez&#39;s curiosity lead learning life</title>
    <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/categories/books/</link>
    <description>Recent content in books on Ramon Suarez&#39;s curiosity lead learning life</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 08:41:19 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ramonsuarez.github.io/categories/books/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Traction (EOS) Book Summary and Review</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/traction-eos-book-summary-and-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 08:41:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/traction-eos-book-summary-and-review/</guid>
      <description>I’ve had to remove all pictures publicly available in other sites, even the promotional picture of the author used in his Amazon profile.
I’ve had to update the capitalization of words to match their style guides, although I do not work for them.
I’ve had to add copyright and trademark symbols all over the place although they are not even mandatory to use and, the TM are not registered (they are just claiming them) and many of them will never be able to be registered because they are just common words being used in a common sense.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kids Are Worth It Summary and Review</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/kids-are-worth-it-summary-and-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 09:05:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/kids-are-worth-it-summary-and-review/</guid>
      <description>Kids Are Worth It: Giving Your Child the Gift of Inner Discipline is important because of its message and ideas to produce responsible and independent human beings. It applies to children and I find it helpful for myself and my relations with adults (also in the workplace). Being a good father is one of my aspirational life goals . Reading books and implementing what I learn are some of my tools to become better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>12 Week Year Summary and Review</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/12-week-year-summary-and-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2019 11:46:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/12-week-year-summary-and-review/</guid>
      <description>The first of my book summary and review series has to be the book that has helped me to finally write down my vision and start a plan to move towards the future I want: The 12 Week Year: Get More Done in 12 Weeks than Others Do in 12 Months by Brian P. Moran and Michael Lennington.
The basic premise of the book is that yearly deadlines are way too long and that we tend to slack until the last minute, wasting too much time and having no time to maneuver left.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Project: Shooting Journal</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/new-project-shooting-journal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 16:27:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/new-project-shooting-journal/</guid>
      <description>Since the last time… Last week I spent time going through my business ideation framework and came up with twenty some new ideas easily. I also came up with new questions accelerate the process. The time frame was too short to be able to really work on improving the framework a lot, but at least I improved the spreadsheet to organize the ideas.
So mixed success in last week’s project and now a new challenge.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
