<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>webmission on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/tags/webmission/</link>
    <description>Recent content in webmission on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2012 09:25:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.ramonsuarez.com/tags/webmission/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Belgian Startups at #LeWeb12 (aka #beleweb)</title>
      <link>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/belgian-startups-at-leweb12-aka-beleweb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2012 09:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/belgian-startups-at-leweb12-aka-beleweb/</guid>
      <description>For the second year on a row there will be a unified Belgian startups stand at LeWeb. On this occassion there will be 15 startups participating from the three Belgian regions: 14 as part of the Startups.be #beleweb delegation and one in the startup competition (Jini). I will also be there as an official blogger, writing mostly for the Spanish internet business blog Loogic.
87seconds 8thColor Carambla CleverPhone EarlyTracks Freedelity Jini MyMicroInvest Small Town Heroes TagTagCity Tuzzit Twipe Mobile Uniwan WeePee </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talking Webmission at WIF Belgium 2010 in Namur</title>
      <link>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/talking-webmission-at-wif-belgium-2010-in-nam/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2010 16:11:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/talking-webmission-at-wif-belgium-2010-in-nam/</guid>
      <description>It was a great occasion to get out of Brussels and see some new web-heads. Always looking forward to it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Webmission: The Belgians Are Coming!</title>
      <link>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/webmission-the-belgians-are-coming/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2010 09:38:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/webmission-the-belgians-are-coming/</guid>
      <description>This is the executive summary of the Webmission that we are sending out to promote our next mission to San Franciso in May 2010, together with three article examples. It is a working document and as such will be evolving. The list of candidates to present their companies is growing and so is the group of entrepreneurs that will also come along but do not have a project to present in a public event.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Webmission #1 to San Francisco. Don&amp;#8217;t you want to join this year?</title>
      <link>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/video-webmission-1-to-san-francisco-dont-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2010 09:26:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/video-webmission-1-to-san-francisco-dont-you/</guid>
      <description>Thanks to Sam Piroton for editing and posting the video!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Webmission, construyendo la Europa de los emprendedores en EBE09</title>
      <link>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/webmission-construyendo-la-europa-de-los-empr/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2009 15:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/webmission-construyendo-la-europa-de-los-empr/</guid>
      <description>Y más gracias todavía a Benito por su comentario. Así dan más ganas de hacer cosas:
Benito dijo:
4 Diciembre 2009 at 4:08 pm
Aun a riesgo de poder participar en un pequeño ‘juego floral’del estilo de, y tu más, tu rosal es más fresco y más oloroso que mis claveles, no puedo más que responderle a Ramón con un gracias.
Como parte de la organización de EBE, Ramón conectó con nosotros con entusiasmo y con buenas ideas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Webmission&amp;#8217;s family picture</title>
      <link>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/the-webmissions-family-picture/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2009 13:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/the-webmissions-family-picture/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
