<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>email marketing automation on Ramon Suarez&#39;s curiosity lead learning life</title>
    <link>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/tags/email-marketing-automation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in email marketing automation on Ramon Suarez&#39;s curiosity lead learning life</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 11:09:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://test.ramonsuarez.com/tags/email-marketing-automation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Results of the Email Reactivation &amp;#038; Segmentation  campaign (&gt;11k emails sent)</title>
      <link>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/results-of-the-email-reactivation-segmentation-campaign-11k-emails-sent/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 11:09:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/results-of-the-email-reactivation-segmentation-campaign-11k-emails-sent/</guid>
      <description>Super Positive Emails The best thing I’ve gotten out of this email blast are a lot of positive emails from people I have not spoken to in a while. They’ve been motivating and great to catch up with. Some of them have ended up in lunches and meetings that have just been great. I got a lot of love!
One of the most unexpected and motivating emails came from my father in law, Graziano.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update: Coworking Courses, Email Segmentation, Meditation Goals</title>
      <link>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/update-coworking-courses-email-segmentation-meditation-goals/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 11:38:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/update-coworking-courses-email-segmentation-meditation-goals/</guid>
      <description>Coworking Courses This week I launched a poll to the members of The Coworking Handbook Newsletter asking them for their priorities for a coworking course: sales or community. The answer was a clear both, so I’ve started both of them.
To learn the ropes and get my hand dirtied I’ve chosen to go first with the coworking community course. It is much shorter than the sales course so it will be easier to finish and launch it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update: Email Marketing, Repurposing, Outsourcing, Automation</title>
      <link>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/update-email-marketing-repurposing-outsourcing-automation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Nov 2018 14:51:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/update-email-marketing-repurposing-outsourcing-automation/</guid>
      <description>Another busy and motivating week has just gone by and things are looking good. Here is this week’s progress report.
As Ash Maurya says:
Practice Trumps Theory
One of the main reasons for the entrepreneurship challenge is to get my hands dirty and it is working wonders.
Revamping Network and Mailing Lists So far 1479 emails of the segmentation project have gone out. The few responses I’m getting are extremely positive and I’ve had my first meeting thanks to it today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Email Segmentation Campaign Is Rolling!</title>
      <link>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/the-email-segmentation-campaign-is-rolling/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 11:37:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/the-email-segmentation-campaign-is-rolling/</guid>
      <description>The email segmentation &amp;amp; reactivation campaign to freshen up my mailing lists is set up and rolling.
Choosing the Right Tool and Cleaning Up Contacts I dropped Mautic for being too complicated and awful to clean up contacts (the main problem I have with all the CRM I’ve tried so far). At the end I went for a much easier set up with the help of a Google add-on by Amit Argawal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dipping My Toes into Email Marketing Automation</title>
      <link>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/dipping-my-toes-into-email-marketing-automation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Oct 2018 18:51:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://test.ramonsuarez.com/dipping-my-toes-into-email-marketing-automation/</guid>
      <description>As part of my entrepreneurship challenge, I’m now dipping my toes into email marketing automation to take advantage of all the contacts I’ve collected through the years and try to deliver value to them based on their interests.
So far I’ve imported over 25.000 contacts to Mautic and a few of the imports are still on hold. There will have to be a major cleaning afterwards. I feel a bit like the star of Going Postal, overwhelmed by the amount of mail to deliver.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
