<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>coworking community course on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/tags/coworking-community-course/</link>
    <description>Recent content in coworking community course on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2019 13:14:51 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.ramonsuarez.com/tags/coworking-community-course/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Flop: Sales Acceleration</title>
      <link>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/flop-sales-acceleration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2019 13:14:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/flop-sales-acceleration/</guid>
      <description>The sales acceleration project has been a real flop.
BIGF Method My biggest effort was on the BIGF Method and it did not really pay much: one extra paying customer and only 26 free customers.
I reached out to my contacts, got a post about my ideation method published in Spain, run ads on Quora and Google…
There are a few factors to consider for this flop:
The original landing page that I contracted via Fiverr did not work at all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First 12 Week Year in Review</title>
      <link>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/my-first-12-week-year-in-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2019 12:19:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/my-first-12-week-year-in-review/</guid>
      <description>Since the launch of my first 12 week year a lot of things have happened and I’ve been able to continue churning out projects as part of my challenge.
12 Week Year One Results Projects The core of this three month year has been the projects and it has worked well. I’ve worked on other projects too (like the Target Shooting Journal), but the core of the challenge has been kept alive through:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flop # 3: Coworking Course Post-Mortem</title>
      <link>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/fail-3-coworking-course-post-mortem/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 15:54:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/fail-3-coworking-course-post-mortem/</guid>
      <description>After all the ins and outs of this course, only 4 people signed up. This is far from the target of 10 that I committed to in mastermind/accountability group. So I cancelled it, reimbursed everybody and closed my account in the e-learning platform (I don’t know if I will release it again nor when). In fact this puts on hold the other coworking courses I had in mind (marketing and sales).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ins and Outs of the  Coworking Course Launch</title>
      <link>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/coworking-course-launched/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 15:19:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/coworking-course-launched/</guid>
      <description>It took a while, but the coworking community course has finally been launched. I kept my timing and the email announcing it went out last Thursday.
Doing a text only course was a good choice. It is much easier to work and rework the content and I can make the delivery much faster. The students have to put their time into doing the tasks to improve their own coworking space community, not on trying to understand my accent in a video.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Morphing: Online Text Course</title>
      <link>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/project-morphing-online-text-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2019 12:32:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/project-morphing-online-text-course/</guid>
      <description>I’m not good with video yet, but there are many other delivery methods to share valuable content and help many people. So I’m going to continue working on the Coworking Community Course with a text only course.
The core of the course is ready, I have about 130 slides with a mix of information and exercises. It is a workbook focused on getting coworking space operators to take actions that will help them build a vibrant and healthy communities while they are taking the course and that will give provide a toolbox they can keep on using and referring to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting over Procrastination and Creator&amp;#8217;s Block</title>
      <link>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/getting-over-procrastination-and-creators-block/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 15:16:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/getting-over-procrastination-and-creators-block/</guid>
      <description>Two things have contributed to this:
Creator’s block Self confidence Creator’s Block Making and online course is a creator challenge. Even if I’m using the content of my coworking book as the base, I’m adding a lot of content and I’m drafting it for video delivery.
I have a lot of experience writing, but not writing for video. Long gone are my days at Canal + in Spain where I was asked to do some writing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update: Coworking Courses, Email Segmentation, Meditation Goals</title>
      <link>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/update-coworking-courses-email-segmentation-meditation-goals/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 11:38:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/update-coworking-courses-email-segmentation-meditation-goals/</guid>
      <description>Coworking Courses This week I launched a poll to the members of The Coworking Handbook Newsletter asking them for their priorities for a coworking course: sales or community. The answer was a clear both, so I’ve started both of them.
To learn the ropes and get my hand dirtied I’ve chosen to go first with the coworking community course. It is much shorter than the sales course so it will be easier to finish and launch it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
