<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>belgianstartups on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/tags/belgianstartups/</link>
    <description>Recent content in belgianstartups on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2012 15:34:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.ramonsuarez.com/tags/belgianstartups/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Thank you Jean !</title>
      <link>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/thank-you-jean/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2012 15:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/thank-you-jean/</guid>
      <description>At the same time Leo Exter was running a Betainvest event upstairs, with 30 investors an 10 startups pitching for funds.
And then Jean dropped the bomb Jean Derely got on an improvised stage to thank the sponsors and go through all the things that have happened in the last 4 years, and then proceeded to drop the bomb: Jean will no longer run the Betagroup.
I cannot say it was a surprise for me or the other members of the Betagroup team (we had been working on his decision for about a month), but it was still a sad moment for me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smarter than Siri: Jini, a proactive personal assistant on your smartphone</title>
      <link>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/smarter-than-siri-jini-a-proactive-personal-a/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2012 08:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/smarter-than-siri-jini-a-proactive-personal-a/</guid>
      <description>Jini is an application for smartphones that proactively sugests you things to do based on other applications usage (like RunKeeper) and the sensor information from your phone (location, speed, light…)
Filip Maertens is the founder of this Belgian startup that can really change our mobile world. A good example of what Jini does: when he arrived to Paris to present at the Startup competition at LeWeb, Jini sugested a route to go jogging close to his hotel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TUZZit: the CheckThis of online project management</title>
      <link>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/tuzzit-the-checkthis-of-online-project-manage/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2012 16:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/tuzzit-the-checkthis-of-online-project-manage/</guid>
      <description>TUZZit is a very promising online project management tool that focuses in ease of use and visual appeal. There are no save buttons and it allows to present ideas and task just like we would do in a whiteboard, with a visual organization instead of a date or alphabet based presentation.
When Christophe Fruyter showed it to me at the Belgian Startups stand at LeWeb, I inmediately thought of CheckThis, the online tool to publish your internet posters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Belgian Startups at #LeWeb12 (aka #beleweb)</title>
      <link>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/belgian-startups-at-leweb12-aka-beleweb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2012 09:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/belgian-startups-at-leweb12-aka-beleweb/</guid>
      <description>For the second year on a row there will be a unified Belgian startups stand at LeWeb. On this occassion there will be 15 startups participating from the three Belgian regions: 14 as part of the Startups.be #beleweb delegation and one in the startup competition (Jini). I will also be there as an official blogger, writing mostly for the Spanish internet business blog Loogic.
87seconds 8thColor Carambla CleverPhone EarlyTracks Freedelity Jini MyMicroInvest Small Town Heroes TagTagCity Tuzzit Twipe Mobile Uniwan WeePee </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
