<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>english on Ramon Suarez&#39;s curiosity lead learning life</title>
    <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/tags/english/</link>
    <description>Recent content in english on Ramon Suarez&#39;s curiosity lead learning life</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2013 12:40:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ramonsuarez.github.io/tags/english/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>I&amp;#8217;m Ramon Suarez, and this is how I work</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/im-ramon-suarez-and-this-is-how-i-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2013 12:40:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/im-ramon-suarez-and-this-is-how-i-work/</guid>
      <description>One of my reference blogs, LifeHacker, has launched an initiative to get more people to share how they work, a series that they have been doing for some time with known startup &amp;amp; Internet people. Hopefully there will be some good tips here for others like me that are continuously looking to hack their lives to make them better.
For those that do not know me, I’ve had an eclectic professional experience working as a journalist, producer, political adviser, marketer, and entrepreneur.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Startups.be the one stop shop for Belgian startups looking for support</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/startups-be-the-one-stop-shop-for-belgian-startups-looking-for-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2013 16:08:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/startups-be-the-one-stop-shop-for-belgian-startups-looking-for-support/</guid>
      <description>If you follow me on Twitter or any other social media account, I’m one of the founders and board members of Startups.be. It is an initiative I’ve been involved in for over a year, but only recently have we created the non profit organization. (Yes, I know it is hard to follow up on all the things I do, but you can always check my LinkedIn to have an idea.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brands, learn about your audience&amp;#8217;s personality with Whit.li</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/brands-learn-about-your-audiences-personality-with-whit-li/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2013 10:18:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/brands-learn-about-your-audiences-personality-with-whit-li/</guid>
      <description>This year I had the chance to catch up with Andy Gillentine and Jack Holt, cofounders of Whit.li, to see what had happened since the Whit.li API was released. It allowed to check compatibility of two people based on the analysis of their social media profiles, and the target companies to use this service where collaborative consumption sites like AirBnB. The talks with the participants then and the follow up meetings taught them that the people who were really interested were brands, advertising and media companies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LDLC-Pro has broken my computer and blames it on me #fail</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/ldlc-pro-has-broken-my-computer-and-blames-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2013 13:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/ldlc-pro-has-broken-my-computer-and-blames-it/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been unlucky enough to start buying at LDLC-Pro my IT material. They had a good reputation and based on it I went ahead and bought a computer, plus an extra SSD disc for another computer, plus some other stuff. It took them a bit longer than expected to deliver, but I was in no hurry so no big deal.
Then my SSD disc failed, and you know how it is: catastrophic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How can market signals contribute to public startup funding?</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/how-can-market-signals-contribute-to-public-s/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2013 16:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/how-can-market-signals-contribute-to-public-s/</guid>
      <description>One of the things that we discussed is how should to ensure that public funding on early stage startups does not bias the market, incentivising “good” ideas that nobody really cares about and ignoring others that are more needed.
My proposal, shared by other participants, is to follow market signals, so that it is the market that chooses and the public sector only reenforces those choices.
But the question is, which market signals?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank you Jean !</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/thank-you-jean/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2012 15:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/thank-you-jean/</guid>
      <description>At the same time Leo Exter was running a Betainvest event upstairs, with 30 investors an 10 startups pitching for funds.
And then Jean dropped the bomb Jean Derely got on an improvised stage to thank the sponsors and go through all the things that have happened in the last 4 years, and then proceeded to drop the bomb: Jean will no longer run the Betagroup.
I cannot say it was a surprise for me or the other members of the Betagroup team (we had been working on his decision for about a month), but it was still a sad moment for me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PeerReach: find and understand social media influencers</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/peerreach-find-and-understand-social-media-in/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2012 11:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/peerreach-find-and-understand-social-media-in/</guid>
      <description>PeerReach is a tool to find the influencers in a topic, language and geographic area. But it does more than help you find them, it helps you understand their main areas of interest and influence in each one of them.
You probably thought of other tools that are stablished in the market- like Klout, PeerIndex and Kredly- that already do something similar. These competitors are focused on their ranking number and are not so good in defining the right areas of interest and influence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>kwiqly: improve the energy use of your building withouth installing hardware</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/kwiqly-improve-the-energy-use-of-your-buildin/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2012 09:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/kwiqly-improve-the-energy-use-of-your-buildin/</guid>
      <description>kwiqly wants to help you save energy money by using the data from your utility provider and combining it with the weather information. There’s nothing to install, no need to buy any hardware.
James Ferguson, has presented the company at the startup competition at LeWeb and they are one of my candidates for the final.
Subscribe to my channel for more tech startup videos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Be-Bound: surf the internet without WiFi or data connectivity</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/be-bound-surf-the-internet-without-wifi-or-da/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2012 09:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/be-bound-surf-the-internet-without-wifi-or-da/</guid>
      <description>Be-Bound is the great world changer of the startup competition at LeWeb. They propose a smarphone app that relies on the standard mobile phone networks to allow for Internet use. How do they do it? By sending sms to and from their servers.
To use it you buy prepaid credit and every action (reading an email, forwarding a message, updating your Twitter timeline), costs from one to three credits.
This application can really be useful on areas with no data coverage and for people traveling to other countries that don’t want to pay the hefty roaming data fees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smarter than Siri: Jini, a proactive personal assistant on your smartphone</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/smarter-than-siri-jini-a-proactive-personal-a/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2012 08:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/smarter-than-siri-jini-a-proactive-personal-a/</guid>
      <description>Jini is an application for smartphones that proactively sugests you things to do based on other applications usage (like RunKeeper) and the sensor information from your phone (location, speed, light…)
Filip Maertens is the founder of this Belgian startup that can really change our mobile world. A good example of what Jini does: when he arrived to Paris to present at the Startup competition at LeWeb, Jini sugested a route to go jogging close to his hotel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TUZZit: the CheckThis of online project management</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/tuzzit-the-checkthis-of-online-project-manage/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2012 16:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/tuzzit-the-checkthis-of-online-project-manage/</guid>
      <description>TUZZit is a very promising online project management tool that focuses in ease of use and visual appeal. There are no save buttons and it allows to present ideas and task just like we would do in a whiteboard, with a visual organization instead of a date or alphabet based presentation.
When Christophe Fruyter showed it to me at the Belgian Startups stand at LeWeb, I inmediately thought of CheckThis, the online tool to publish your internet posters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Belgian Startups at #LeWeb12 (aka #beleweb)</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/belgian-startups-at-leweb12-aka-beleweb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2012 09:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/belgian-startups-at-leweb12-aka-beleweb/</guid>
      <description>For the second year on a row there will be a unified Belgian startups stand at LeWeb. On this occassion there will be 15 startups participating from the three Belgian regions: 14 as part of the Startups.be #beleweb delegation and one in the startup competition (Jini). I will also be there as an official blogger, writing mostly for the Spanish internet business blog Loogic.
87seconds 8thColor Carambla CleverPhone EarlyTracks Freedelity Jini MyMicroInvest Small Town Heroes TagTagCity Tuzzit Twipe Mobile Uniwan WeePee </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Custom 3D Printing &amp;#038; Marketplace For Your Designs : iMaterialise</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/custom-3d-printing-marketplace-for-your-desig/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2012 08:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/custom-3d-printing-marketplace-for-your-desig/</guid>
      <description>At the last TEDxLeuven I was gratefully surprised: I found out about Materialise, a world leader and pioneer in industrial 3D printing, which comes out of Belgium. One more of the leading tech companies that not so many people have ever heard about, but which is responsible for the printing of most personalized ear implants in the world.
Luckily for me they had a stand at MultiMania and I got a chance to talk with them and to hold and examine some of the printed objects they had with them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is it worth it to post startup videos outside YouTube?</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/is-it-worth-it-to-post-startup-videos-outside/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2012 20:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/is-it-worth-it-to-post-startup-videos-outside/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Startups Mega Event in Brussels: Startups.be</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/tech-startups-mega-event-in-brussels-startups/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2012 12:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/tech-startups-mega-event-in-brussels-startups/</guid>
      <description>The event starts at 2pm and will go on until the night, with some drinks after a Betagroup Pitch Slam. My experience tells me that it will end up even later with informal dinners going on until late.
You do not have to attend the full event, just go to the parts that interest you or can attend. It is free and you just have to sign up here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Artist: lessons for entrepreneurs (don&amp;#8217;t do as The Muppets do)</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/the-artist-lessons-for-entrepreneurs-dont-do/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Mar 2012 21:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/the-artist-lessons-for-entrepreneurs-dont-do/</guid>
      <description>You never know who’s gonna be who or where you are going to end Don’t treat those that are not yet somebody with disrespect. Even when I worked in public affairs this was a must. You never know where people are going to be at next. You cannot know everything about everybody, specially of those that you just met or haven’t had the time to get acquainted yet. Today’s trainee, junior employee or young entrepreneur could be tomorrow’s big thing, not in the long time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I guess this is an automatic translation of my profile from Polish</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/i-guess-this-is-an-automatic-translation-of-m/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2011 08:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/i-guess-this-is-an-automatic-translation-of-m/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interview about the Founder Institute in Tech Brew Podcast [Audio]</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/interview-about-the-founder-institute-in-tech/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2011 15:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/interview-about-the-founder-institute-in-tech/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Great Definition of Coworking</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/a-great-definition-of-coworking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2011 08:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/a-great-definition-of-coworking/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FI: Pitch Bootcamp in Brussels with Filip Tack</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/fi-pitch-bootcamp-in-brussels-with-filip-tack/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2011 07:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/fi-pitch-bootcamp-in-brussels-with-filip-tack/</guid>
      <description>This is my first event as director of the Founder Insitute in Brussels. I’m really looking forward to it. Filip is amazing and I’m sure that the ideas that people will pitch are also gonna be fantastic (and a great way to prepare for Startup Weekend Brussels!)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Entrepreneurship &amp;#038; Coworking: Interviews by Fred Ooms</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/entrepreneurship-coworking-interviews-by-fred/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2011 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/entrepreneurship-coworking-interviews-by-fred/</guid>
      <description>Fred Ooms has just finished publishing the interview we had a couple months ago. It was really nice to have some time to talk entrepreneurship with somebody like Fred, alumnus of MBA Solvay like myself, and also working with a university to try to bring part of their research knowledge and patents to market. We just set up a video call and got the interview rolling. Nice, lean and true. In his blog you can find a great selection of entrepreneurship video interviews.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Two &#43; One Must Read Internet Business Books</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/two-one-must-read-internet-business-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2011 13:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/two-one-must-read-internet-business-book/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What pushed Jean and Ramon to open the Betagroup Coworking Brussels (Betacowork)</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/what-pushed-jean-and-ramon-to-open-the-betagr/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2011 13:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/what-pushed-jean-and-ramon-to-open-the-betagr/</guid>
      <description>Thanks Fred!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great Linux Multitouch Multiscreen: Skin by uma information technologies</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/great-multitouch-multiscreen-skin-by-uma-info/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 May 2011 07:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/great-multitouch-multiscreen-skin-by-uma-info/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Real Digital Natives: 80% of Children Under Age 5 Use the Internet [STATS]</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/the-real-digital-natives-80-of-children-under/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2011 09:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/the-real-digital-natives-80-of-children-under/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mobile Use in the UK &amp;#038; Germany Infographic</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/mobile-use-in-the-uk-germany-infographic/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2011 08:51:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/mobile-use-in-the-uk-germany-infographic/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Internet Promotes Intimacy (Stefana Broadbent)</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/internet-promotes-intimacy-stefana-broadbent/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2011 10:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/internet-promotes-intimacy-stefana-broadbent/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Looking forward to the next Betagroup Pitch-Slam</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/looking-forward-to-the-next-betagroup-pitch-s/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2011 16:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/looking-forward-to-the-next-betagroup-pitch-s/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Choosing the Right Channel to Request Attention</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/choosing-the-right-channel-to-request-attenti/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2011 09:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/choosing-the-right-channel-to-request-attenti/</guid>
      <description> The communication channnel choice is complex and does not depend on cost. The more attention it requires, the less people we interact with regularly. The two extremes of the table are Skype video conversations (3) and Facebook/Twitter broadcasting (100+) Cultural impact of availability on the choice of channel: the bussier the other person is, the less we will use a highly synchronous channel like phone or Skype. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interviews about MBA Solvay: A Life Changing Experience</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/interview-about-mba-solvay-a-life-changing-ex/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2011 14:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/interview-about-mba-solvay-a-life-changing-ex/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Geekin&amp;#8217; and eatin&amp;#8217; at the Betagroup Coworking Brussels (AKA Betacowork)</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/geekin-and-eatin-at-the-betagroup-coworking-b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2011 15:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/geekin-and-eatin-at-the-betagroup-coworking-b/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Betagroup Presentation Template to Pitch to Investors</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/betagroup-presentation-guidelines-to-pitch-to/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2011 15:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/betagroup-presentation-guidelines-to-pitch-to/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 6 Principles of Influence (Must Read)</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/the-6-principles-of-influence-must-read/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2011 08:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/the-6-principles-of-influence-must-read/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>??Mi pueblo! My Town! Mon Village!</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/mi-pueblo-my-town-mon-village/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2011 07:46:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/mi-pueblo-my-town-mon-village/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Content Farm Strategy: AOL&amp;#8217;s Master Plan</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/content-farm-strategy-aols-master-plan/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Feb 2011 10:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/content-farm-strategy-aols-master-plan/</guid>
      <description>Paying peanuts per post is way too common right now, if the posts are not just free. The worst of it is the lack of sustainability of this model that leads to an ever decreasing number of journalists and bloggers, standardization of news, lack of research, reduction of sources and amateurization of the whole writing business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kodesk Debrief After Winning Startup Weekend Brussels 2011</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/kodesk-debrief-after-winning-startup-weekend/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2011 11:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/kodesk-debrief-after-winning-startup-weekend/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mission cuisine at the Betagroup Coworking Brussels</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/mission-cuisine-at-the-betagroup-coworking-br/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2011 11:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/mission-cuisine-at-the-betagroup-coworking-br/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lets get the night started! #swbru</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/lets-get-the-night-started-swbru/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2011 18:45:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/lets-get-the-night-started-swbru/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Startup Weekend Brussels Idea List (and Finalists) | Startup Weekend Brussels</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/the-startup-weekend-brussels-idea-list-and-fi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2011 14:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/the-startup-weekend-brussels-idea-list-and-fi/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 5 elements of Inspirational leadership, by @harleylovegrove</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/the-5-elements-of-inspirational-leadership-by/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jan 2011 08:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/the-5-elements-of-inspirational-leadership-by/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>11 finalist Startup Weekend Brussels #swbru</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/11-finalist-startup-weekend-brussels-swbru/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2011 21:14:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/11-finalist-startup-weekend-brussels-swbru/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Voting time ! #swbru</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/voting-time-swbru/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2011 20:49:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/voting-time-swbru/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>46 ideas pitched at #swbru :-)</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/46-ideas-pitched-at-swbru/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2011 19:59:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/46-ideas-pitched-at-swbru/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Full house at #swbru !</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/full-house-at-swbru/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2011 18:24:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/full-house-at-swbru/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Social Meedia to Boost Business</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/using-social-meedia-to-boost-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2011 16:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/using-social-meedia-to-boost-business/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>xpats Portraits: Ramon Suarez (The Bulletin)</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/xpats-portraits-ramon-suarez-the-bulletin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2011 14:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/xpats-portraits-ramon-suarez-the-bulletin/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2010: the year in internet stats</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/2010-the-year-in-internet-stats/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2011 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/2010-the-year-in-internet-stats/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Launch Your Startup In 54 Hours</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/launch-your-startup-in-54-hours/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2011 13:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/launch-your-startup-in-54-hours/</guid>
      <description>First Startup Weekend in Belgium Launch Your Startup in 54 hours For the first time in Belgium, 80 people will get together in Brussels to turn their ideas into running startups over the course of the Startup Weekend Brussels: from idea to startup in just 54 hours.
Startup Weekend starts on Friday evening with participants presenting (pitching) their startup ideas. The participants (a mix of developers, designers, and business professionals) vote on the best ideas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Already 30 tickets sold for Startup Weekend Brussels. Get yours before it is too late!</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/already-30-tickets-sold-for-startup-weekend-b/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2011 09:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/already-30-tickets-sold-for-startup-weekend-b/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Only 15 days to Startup Weekend Brussels</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/only-15-days-to-startup-weekend-brussels/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2011 09:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/only-15-days-to-startup-weekend-brussels/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Facebook Use 2010: Yearly &amp;#038; Daily User Stats</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/facebook-use-2010-yearly-stats/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2011 16:30:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/facebook-use-2010-yearly-stats/</guid>
      <description>Facebook Usage Stats 2010* Minutes in a year 525,949 20 min blocks in year 26,297 Av. Users (estimate) 500,000,000 Days in a year 365 Yearly Per User Per User &amp;amp; Day Shared links: 26,297,438,300 53 0.14 Tagged photos: 34,791,510,871 70 0.19 Event invites sent out: 39,025,398,437 78 0.21 Wall posts: 41,734,034,582 83 0.23 Status updates: 48,676,558,293 97 0.27 Friend requests accepted: 51,858,548,328 104 0.28 Photos uploaded: 71,423,842,423 143 0.39 Comments: 268,444,250,166 537 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Facebook in 2010 &amp;#8211; The Top 30 Most Useful Blog Posts on Facebook</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/facebook-in-2010-the-top-30-most-useful-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2010 21:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/facebook-in-2010-the-top-30-most-useful-blog/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Open Internet: A Case for Net Neutrality</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/the-open-internet-a-case-for-net-neutrality/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2010 21:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/the-open-internet-a-case-for-net-neutrality/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Facebook International Friendship Beauty</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/facebook-international-friendship-beauty/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2010 09:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/facebook-international-friendship-beauty/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>State of The Blogosphere in 2010 (infographic)</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/state-of-the-blogosphere-in-2010-infographic/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2010 08:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/state-of-the-blogosphere-in-2010-infographic/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 things you should know about Internet, but no one ever told you-2010 version</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/10-things-you-should-know-but-no-one-ever-tol/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2010 17:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/10-things-you-should-know-but-no-one-ever-tol/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great Video: iMinds 2010</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/great-video-iminds-2010/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2010 16:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/great-video-iminds-2010/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>180?? Panorama of the BetaGroup Cowork in Brussels</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/360-panorama-of-the-betagroup-cowork-in-bruss/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2010 17:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/360-panorama-of-the-betagroup-cowork-in-bruss/</guid>
      <description>Thanks to @xdamman the newest member coming to cowork in Brussels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LeWeb Startup Competition Winners</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/35837555/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2010 16:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/35837555/</guid>
      <description>Out of the 16 startups that where selected to compete at LeWeb10, the 3 finalists have been awarded a price each:
Virality prize: Paper.Li
Technology prize: Waze
Originality prize: Super Marmite
Prize of the audience: Deways</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Renault to Rent the Batteries of Its New Electric Cars</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/renault-to-rent-the-batteries-of-its-new-elec/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2010 08:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/renault-to-rent-the-batteries-of-its-new-elec/</guid>
      <description>Renault is bringing an interesting business model to the market with its new electric cars: they will sell the cars and rent the batteries. Advantages for the users: no worries about lifetime of the batteries, recycling taken care of by the company. Advantage for the company: recurring revenue and stronger bond with clients.
Matthieu Tenenbaum, deputy electric car program director, presents the new electric cars (Twizy, Fluence and Dezire), and talks about the business model and partnerships with cities and corporations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I love @bnox &amp;#8216;s computer</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/i-love-bnox-s-computer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2010 08:33:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/i-love-bnox-s-computer/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Want To Drive a Twizy at #LeWeb10 !</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/i-want-to-drive-a-twizy-at-leweb10/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2010 09:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/i-want-to-drive-a-twizy-at-leweb10/</guid>
      <description>If you know me, you know I hate driving. But I really want to drive a Twizy electric city car (no driving license needed.) I will be test driving a Fluence later on the day.
Disclosure: Renault pays for my travel and lodging in Paris for LeWeb, but I&amp;rsquo;m publishing what I want and when I want 🙂 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Impressive room at #LeWeb10</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/impressive-room-at-leweb10/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2010 08:51:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/impressive-room-at-leweb10/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When???s the Best Time to Publish Blog Posts?</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/whens-the-best-time-to-publish-blog-posts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2010 20:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/whens-the-best-time-to-publish-blog-posts/</guid>
      <description> Publish often, more than once a day Keep your best posts for Friday morning and early afternoon </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TEDxBrussels 2010 Program (Google Docs)</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/tedxbrussels-2010-program-google-docs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2010 17:44:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/tedxbrussels-2010-program-google-docs/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Live Streaming #LeWeb10 (Plus Social Streams)</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/live/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2010 17:23:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/live/</guid>
      <description>For those that can not make it to LeWeb this year, an easy way to watch the plenary and the startup competition and to follow what is said about it in social media. You can also track the hashtags #leweb10 and #leweb. I will be watching all this live in Paris, twitting about it (follow @ramonsuarez) and hopefully also blogging right here at ramonsuarez.com. Enjoy!
The Plenary Startup Competition ( dec 8th ) &amp;amp; Plenary II ( dec 9th ) </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cobot Business Model (Lean Startup Canvas)</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/cobot-business-model-lean-startup-canvas/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2010 22:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/cobot-business-model-lean-startup-canvas/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lo??c Le Meur &amp;#038; LeWeb10 (interview)</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/loic-le-meur-leweb10-interview/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2010 10:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/loic-le-meur-leweb10-interview/</guid>
      <description>These are the responses given by Loïc to the short questionnary I sent him. He was really quick tp answer!
What is LeWeb like for Loïc Le Meur? LeWeb is a tool box for the european entpreneur: from the inspiration to find ideas to start a business to networking with Google, Microsoft or Facebook and raising angel or VC money. They can do it all during two days. This year we even have a “how to get acquired” panel to help them understand how to sell their business if they like.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Networking tips in time for #LeWeb10</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/networking-tips-in-time-for-leweb10/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2010 22:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/networking-tips-in-time-for-leweb10/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open House &#43; TedX Ticket</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/open-house-tedx-ticket/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2010 17:47:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/open-house-tedx-ticket/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video: BetaGroup Pitch Slam at Digital Marketing First in Brussels</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/video-betagroup-pitch-slam-at-digital-marketi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2010 08:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/video-betagroup-pitch-slam-at-digital-marketi/</guid>
      <description>The presenting startups where:
Userplus.comWooRank.comdesktop-reporting.comWataro.comtinkertouch.comadlogix.eudialogfeed.comYou should not miss the presentation by Desktop Reporting (min. 29.55), it managed to get everybody’s attention.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Introduce a Friend to Social Media</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/how-to-introduce-a-friend-to-social-media/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Nov 2010 18:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/how-to-introduce-a-friend-to-social-media/</guid>
      <description>Enjoy!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Influencers, The Movie</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/influencers-the-movie/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2010 14:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/influencers-the-movie/</guid>
      <description>What and who are the influencers?
A conversation starter, via @annmarcelis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The State of Facebook at 500 Million Members (Infographic)</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/the-state-of-facebook-at-500-million-members/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jul 2010 10:47:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/the-state-of-facebook-at-500-million-members/</guid>
      <description>The USA is clearly ahead of all other countries in number of users, with the UK coming in second place with a fifth of the users. Most of the users are over 24 years old and there’s a half and half gender split, with a missing 3% that I wonder if it is made of un-sexed angels.
As a Spaniard living in Belgium there’s two things that have surprised me on the anecdote side: Spain is the 10th country with more Facebook users and Belgium is the 7th oldest country in the social Network.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactive Spanish Media Map</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/interactive-spanish-media-map/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jul 2010 08:22:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/interactive-spanish-media-map/</guid>
      <description>Too bad we can not get a bigger view or print it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>World Domination by Facebook</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/world-domination-by-facebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2010 17:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/world-domination-by-facebook/</guid>
      <description>Play with the world map of social networks to get a more detailed view.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Europe Facebook Usage Statistics Map</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/europe-facebook-usage-statistics-map/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2010 17:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/europe-facebook-usage-statistics-map/</guid>
      <description>I wonder if they count active users or all people that have subscribed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The coming of the Netrenaissance</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/the-coming-of-the-netrenaissance/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2010 07:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/the-coming-of-the-netrenaissance/</guid>
      <description>One of the things that has always amazed me about the Renaissance is how the most famous wise-men of the time had all multiple fields of expertise and interest. They had a focus on learning and education, coming out of a time of obscurity, fighting ignorance, status quo and superstition. Leonardo Da Vinci is a great example having his main source of living in art but also developing his knowledge and inventions in science.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kids Media Use By Platform: TV Rules, Computers Come 3rd</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/kids-media-use-by-platform-tv-rules-computers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2010 13:38:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/kids-media-use-by-platform-tv-rules-computers/</guid>
      <description>Get the full report: Generation M2: Media in the Lives of 8- to 18-Year-Olds and share your understanding of it and your ideas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter in Belgium (infographic)</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/twitter-in-belgium-infographic/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2010 08:33:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/twitter-in-belgium-infographic/</guid>
      <description>The average Twitter account in Belgium follows 90 Twitter users, is followed by 87, is listed 4,5 times, and has tweeted 378 times.
Out of an estimate of 75.000 to 100.000 accounts, 32% Tweet weekly and 18% have no activity at all.
I’m looking forward to more information coming from Bruno about what is going on in this country. Thank you Bruno!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Europe&amp;#8217;s Blooming Tech Entrepreneurs</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/europes-blooming-tech-entrepreneurs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2010 15:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/europes-blooming-tech-entrepreneurs/</guid>
      <description>The two things that struck me the most were:??
The seed and start-up venture capital structure in Europe. The shocking list of the barriers to entrepreneurship index made by the OECD. Italy, Spain and Sweden have lower barriers than the USA. It has also left me thinking about the Venture Capital divide.
Great food for thought.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Android handset manufacturers: stop screwing up the interface (open letter)</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/android-handset-manufacturers-stop-screwing-u/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2010 07:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/android-handset-manufacturers-stop-screwing-u/</guid>
      <description>Dear Android handset manufacturers:??
I understand that you would like to lock-in your users with something more than the hardware you produce, which risks being completely commoditized soon. But please, do yourself and your users a favor and stop screwing up the interface of Android. The user experience with Android needs a lot of refinement still and you are only subtracting from it.??
If you really want to keep a healthy business and prevail over other systems like Apple’s iPhone, what you should do is create an umbrella organization together with Google to help each other produce the best Android interface on earth that will work with all the different devices you make.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google ads, mercenaries and blogs about Brussels</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/google-ads-mercenaries-and-blogs-about-brusse/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2010 07:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/google-ads-mercenaries-and-blogs-about-brusse/</guid>
      <description>Google Ads may not be an excellent source of revenue, but it does pay in laughs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Should You Care About Video on Facebook? The TubeMogul Answer</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/why-should-you-care-about-video-on-facebook-t/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2010 15:21:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/why-should-you-care-about-video-on-facebook-t/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why we do not read email marketing messages: too frequent, irrelevant, spammy</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/why-we-do-not-read-email-marketing-messages-t/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2010 13:01:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/why-we-do-not-read-email-marketing-messages-t/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why are there so many free Android and iPhone mobile apps?</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/why-are-there-so-many-free-android-and-iphone/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2010 10:01:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/why-are-there-so-many-free-android-and-iphone/</guid>
      <description>Because it is much easier to make an app than to sell an app.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beta Group&amp;#8217;s Internet Entrepreneurship Links</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/beta-groups-internet-entrepreneurship-links/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2010 07:24:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/beta-groups-internet-entrepreneurship-links/</guid>
      <description>In case you do not know about it, the Beta Group is the largest Internet &amp;amp; Tech entrepreneurship networking event in Belgium, with about 350 attendees in each of its monthly meetups. The event consists of a pitch slam with six startups showcasing their products, short requests and announcements from the audience (the live tweets), and lots of networking over free warm beer. A must.
Disclosure: I am a member of the Beta Group’s council, and proud of it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A third of Belgium is in Facebook.</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/a-third-of-belgium-is-in-facebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2010 17:41:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/a-third-of-belgium-is-in-facebook/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Fifth of Spain is in Facebook: Stats of Facebook Users in Spain, May 2010</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/a-fifth-of-spain-is-in-facebook-stats-of-face/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jun 2010 16:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/a-fifth-of-spain-is-in-facebook-stats-of-face/</guid>
      <description>Thanks to Ra??l Dorado for sharing the information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>European Blogosphere Stats (Campus Party Europe Presentation)</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/european-blogosphere-stats-campus-party-europ/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2010 09:17:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/european-blogosphere-stats-campus-party-europ/</guid>
      <description>Beyond the great experience of spending a few days in a super-geeky event, I also had the opportunity to prepare with Jonan this study about the perception of the European Blogosphere based on the responses given by European bloggers invited to Campus Party Europe. This is not a scientific work, it is fully subjective but still bears a lot of interesting information that prompted a very interesting debate with my copresenter Ben Hammersley and with the audience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Internet Pornography Stats</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/internet-pornography-stats/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2010 09:37:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/internet-pornography-stats/</guid>
      <description>Thanks to Vincent Battaglia for sharing the link to this stats.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spanish Journalists in Twitter</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/spanish-journalists-in-twitter/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2010 16:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/spanish-journalists-in-twitter/</guid>
      <description>Thanks to Jos?? Luis Orihuela for making such an extensive list and to Rafael Estrella for pointing at it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fred Destin&amp;#8217;s Workshop on Hacking Venture Capital</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/fred-destins-workshop-on-hacking-venture-capi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2010 17:09:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/fred-destins-workshop-on-hacking-venture-capi/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sex, Weapons and Tourism in Facebook Ads</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/sex-weapons-and-tourism-in-facebook-ads/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2010 07:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/sex-weapons-and-tourism-in-facebook-ads/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skype World Stats</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/skype-world-stats/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2010 04:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/skype-world-stats/</guid>
      <description>Skype, when it was still part of eBay, issued quarterly updates but those have now stopped. Nevertheless, here are the latest numbers:
Skype added 39 million registered users in the fourth quarter to end the year with a total of 560 million. The number of Skype-to-Skype call minutes totaled 36.1 billion in the final three months of 2009. Skype users made more the 250 billion minutes worth of Skype-to-Skype calls from the time the service was launched through the end of 2009.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Design Innovation &amp;#038; Future of Internet: Paul Bennet &amp;#038; Ben Hammersley at Campus Party Europe</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/design-innovation-future-of-internet-paul-ben/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2010 10:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/design-innovation-future-of-internet-paul-ben/</guid>
      <description>The Digital Creativity area of Campus Party Europe could not have had a better start. This morning Paul Bennet and Ben Hammersley have given two very interestin presentations about design innovation and the future of Internet. These are the highlights I have retained:
Paul Bennet “Design Innovation” IDEO’s journey current stage is Framing: design redefines the challenges facing organizations.
Design is about change, impact and optimism.
Now dealing with bigger issues: design of everyday life, social interactions &amp;amp; behaviors, countries and societies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ramon&amp;#8217;s Madrid Top 10 Eating and Drinking Spots</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/ramons-madrid-top-10-eating-and-drinking-spot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2010 09:08:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/ramons-madrid-top-10-eating-and-drinking-spot/</guid>
      <description>Here’s the list of my favorite places to eat and drink in Madrid, my much loved hometown. They are all either in the center of the city or within a short bus ride. There are a hell of a lot more good places and you will see that the city is very lively around socializing in bars and restaurants, and above all night life.
If you have time and can read Spanish, I recommend taking a look at the Madrid Tapas’ Guide by Pisto y Nopisto (a refined eating and drinking blog) and this very complete tapas guide.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ramon&amp;#8217;s Vision about the Future of Mobile. Keynote Presentation at Droidcon Belgium 2010</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/ramons-vision-about-the-future-of-mobile-keyn/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2010 14:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/ramons-vision-about-the-future-of-mobile-keyn/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thirst for News in Twitter and Social Networks [STATS]</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/thirst-for-news-in-twitter-and-social-network/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2010 08:03:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/thirst-for-news-in-twitter-and-social-network/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social media engagement means more support and willingness to buy</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/social-media-engagement-means-more-support-an/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2010 08:44:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/social-media-engagement-means-more-support-an/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter Stats Infographic</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/twitter-stats-infographic/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2010 07:02:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/twitter-stats-infographic/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The future is not Free: a Belgian Android example</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/the-future-is-not-free-a-belgian-android-exam/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2010 08:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/the-future-is-not-free-a-belgian-android-exam/</guid>
      <description>[Free](http://www.wired.com/techbiz/it/magazine/16-03/ff_free?currentPage=all &amp;ldquo;Chris Anderson&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Free! Why $0.00 Is the Future of Business&amp;rdquo; article in Wired Magazine&amp;rdquo;) is not the Holy Grail of the Internet. To have a sustainable ecosystem we need to have sources of revenue that do not involve having half the planet using our service. Smaller companies tailoring a product to a smaller audience must charge to sustain their business… and that is good!
Free, for most of the companies, is nothing more than an appetizer to their products and services, it is a marketing tool.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yes, blogging has peaked and it is not a problem</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/yes-blogging-has-peaked-and-it-is-not-a-probl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2010 08:42:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/yes-blogging-has-peaked-and-it-is-not-a-probl/</guid>
      <description>Of all the blogs I follow, only the professional ones keep up the pace. A lot of personal bloggers have stopped writing or greatly reduced their contributions. Why wouldn’t they with Facebook and Twitter’s instant gratification and reduced effort? Why on earth would we have to consider that it is a problem?
Lets face it, most of the personal blogposts are exactly that, personal, and directed to a group of friends: they will be much better served in a less publicly scrutinized platform like Facebook, or Netlog, or Tuenti, or you-name-the-closed-garden-social-network.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leads for less with social media: stats about online marketing costs per lead</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/leads-for-less-with-social-media-stats-about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2010 10:29:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/leads-for-less-with-social-media-stats-about/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video: The state of the Internet in numbers</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/video-the-state-of-the-internet-in-numbers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2010 16:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/video-the-state-of-the-internet-in-numbers/</guid>
      <description>The numbers have been included with all their zeros (taking into account USA numbering) to make it easier to grasp the volumes we are talking about and to try to avoid some of the mistakes that are usually made when transferring billions and trillions from country to country. It will also be easier to do copy and pasting to a spreadsheet program (which sucks in transnational settings.) I have outlined a couple disparities in numbers, which are probably due to rounding and differences in the dates of samples.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Study: Age distribution of social network users in the USA | Royal Pingdom</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/study-age-distribution-of-social-network-user/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2010 10:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/study-age-distribution-of-social-network-user/</guid>
      <description>The average social network user is 37 years old. The dominant age group is 35-44. 79% of users are older than 25 years old. The 18-24 years old group does not top any site I’m sure the European aged distribution of social network users would not be far from this.
Hopefully this will definitely kill the still-heard-off-belief that social networking is for teenagers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talking Webmission at WIF Belgium 2010 in Namur</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/talking-webmission-at-wif-belgium-2010-in-nam/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2010 16:11:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/talking-webmission-at-wif-belgium-2010-in-nam/</guid>
      <description>It was a great occasion to get out of Brussels and see some new web-heads. Always looking forward to it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Webmission: The Belgians Are Coming!</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/webmission-the-belgians-are-coming/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2010 09:38:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/webmission-the-belgians-are-coming/</guid>
      <description>This is the executive summary of the Webmission that we are sending out to promote our next mission to San Franciso in May 2010, together with three article examples. It is a working document and as such will be evolving. The list of candidates to present their companies is growing and so is the group of entrepreneurs that will also come along but do not have a project to present in a public event.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Webmission #1 to San Francisco. Don&amp;#8217;t you want to join this year?</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/video-webmission-1-to-san-francisco-dont-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2010 09:26:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/video-webmission-1-to-san-francisco-dont-you/</guid>
      <description>Thanks to Sam Piroton for editing and posting the video!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do social media owe Kant a tribute? #categories</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/do-social-media-owe-kant-a-tribute-categories/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2010 19:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/do-social-media-owe-kant-a-tribute-categories/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plugg is coming! Great web entrepreneurship speakers in Brussels</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/plugg-is-coming-great-web-entrepreneurship-sp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2010 18:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/plugg-is-coming-great-web-entrepreneurship-sp/</guid>
      <description>Plugg is coming again to Brussels, to celebrate “entrepreneurship and innovation in Europe and raising global awareness for those European start-ups in the Web / Mobile 2.0 field that stand out in the crop”. After my participation last year, I can not wait for this year’s edition on March 11. The quality of the speakers and of the companies participating in the Startup Rally, plus the top-noch European networking make it a must-be for all those interested in Web and Mobile ventures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dreaming of Silicon Valley? Expand Your Business in the USA  workshop in Brussels</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/dreaming-of-silicon-valley-expand-your-busine/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2010 10:06:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/dreaming-of-silicon-valley-expand-your-busine/</guid>
      <description>Thanks to Charles Crouch for pointing to this opportunity at the Beta Group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Search Engine Optimization checklist for DevCom Brussels</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/search-engine-optimization-checklist-for-devc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2010 13:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/search-engine-optimization-checklist-for-devc/</guid>
      <description>Some marketing and communication professionals wrongly despise SEO, considering it just a bunch of technical tricks used to divert Internet users towards sites not worthy of their attention. The truth is that they should look at it from the perspective of their clients: good SEO helps users find the content they are looking for. SEO is not some arkane cult or ritual. Most marketing and communication professionals know some of its basics thanks to their education in journalism, and most of the rest are very easy to imply using a little reasoning and common sense or even better: reading.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Media Conference at DevCom Brussels</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/social-media-conference-at-devcom-brussels/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2010 12:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/social-media-conference-at-devcom-brussels/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Engage your clients using Twitter: Devcom.be demo notes</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/engage-your-clients-using-twitter-devcombe-de/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2010 12:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/engage-your-clients-using-twitter-devcombe-de/</guid>
      <description>Tomorrow I’will be participating in DevCom Brussels, a forum for commercial development in Belgium. Besides networking and getting inspired by the conferences, I will be speaking about social media and also doing 7 minute one to one demos. One of them will be an introduction to Twitter, covering the basic reasons, advantages and things to keep in mind when using it (although these can be applied to all social networks). This are the notes I’ve prepared:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shame on me!</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/shame-on-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2010 18:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/shame-on-me/</guid>
      <description>The inner fight that many times stops some great fresh posts to see the light of the screen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Suggested reading: Manifesto on management 2.0</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/suggested-reading-manifesto-on-management-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2010 09:57:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/suggested-reading-manifesto-on-management-20/</guid>
      <description>Although I agree that the quality of the product is very important, I do not agree with the idea that the product itself is the marketing. This falls into the traditional engineer trap where the creators of a product just concentrate their efforts in the product and disregard marketing.
Without marketing your great product will die in obscurity. There are many forms of marketing and different actions to take depending on your willingness and resources.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 10 commandments of Beta Group presentations</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/the-10-commandments-of-beta-group-presentatio/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2010 17:51:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/the-10-commandments-of-beta-group-presentatio/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>World Map of Social Networks</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/world-map-of-social-networks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2009 11:20:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/world-map-of-social-networks/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Huge visitors difference between Posterous stats and Google Analytics</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/huge-visitors-difference-between-posterous-st/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2009 11:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/huge-visitors-difference-between-posterous-st/</guid>
      <description>The more analytics I see, the more puzzled I am by the disparity among them. In this particular case, the huge difference between Posterous stats and Google Analytics after just one month of publishing.
According to Posterous, this blog has already received 1722 visits. But according to Google Analytics, it has received 294 with 499 page views, of which 222 are unique visitors. I guess that what Posterous counts are pageviews, but still the difference is way too big among them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google&amp;#8217;s Site Management Guidelines</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/googles-site-management-guidelines/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2009 11:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/googles-site-management-guidelines/</guid>
      <description>Easy and brief information that will help you be more relevant and findable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twoddler and the butterfly effect</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/twoddler-and-the-butterfly-effect/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2009 14:52:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/twoddler-and-the-butterfly-effect/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What would your last tweet be like?</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/what-would-your-last-tweet-be-like/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2009 14:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/what-would-your-last-tweet-be-like/</guid>
      <description>You know who it is addressed to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fastest Internet Service Providers in the World: not in Belgium</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/fastest-internet-service-providers-in-the-wor/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2009 12:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/fastest-internet-service-providers-in-the-wor/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Search Engine Ranking Factors 2009</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/search-engine-ranking-factors-2009/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2009 15:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/search-engine-ranking-factors-2009/</guid>
      <description>Good and brief SEO summary from SEOmoz, with the few things not to ever ignore if you want to optimize your search engine results. It is also a good view on the core of Google’s search algorithm.
SEO experts are the new alchimists, always looking for the philosophical stone (Google’s algorithm) to turn their websites into gold.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three things you should never tell a VC when fundraising &amp;#8211; Fred Destin</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/three-things-you-should-never-tell-a-vc-when/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2009 10:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/three-things-you-should-never-tell-a-vc-when/</guid>
      <description>Fred Destin is a VC I follow since I saw his brilliant participation in this roundtable at Plugg in Brussels: VC Panel: Where’s The Money Gone? from Plugg Conference on Vimeo.
He was completely detached at the beginning, but thanks to the arts of Matthäus Krzykowski he ended up getting fully into it and providing for one of the best moments of the conference.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web Conferences Around the Globe</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/web-conferences-around-the-globe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2009 09:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/web-conferences-around-the-globe/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seniors online statistics (US)</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/seniors-online-statistics-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2009 11:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/seniors-online-statistics-us/</guid>
      <description>December 10th, 2009 | by Ben Parr
View comments23 Comments and 719 Reactions
The research confirmed a trend that we’ve seen in recent years: that more seniors are becoming active on the web. In November of 2004, there were 11.3 million active seniors online. In November 2009, that number jumped by 55% to 17.5 million. In addition, they spend more time on the web, totaling an average of 58 hours a month in front of the browser.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Revenge and the unlogical logics of economics</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/revenge-and-the-unlogical-logics-of-economics/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2009 09:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/revenge-and-the-unlogical-logics-of-economics/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enrique Dans and company management: startup model vs traditional companies</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/enrique-dans-and-company-management-startup-m/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2009 16:34:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/enrique-dans-and-company-management-startup-m/</guid>
      <description>On top of it, he is just great. A bloguer at heart, he lives by the principle of sharing knowledge and promotes access to himself with a full disclosure of his contact details.
A lot of people talk the talk, Enrique walks the walk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 5 Blogging Misconceptions</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/top-5-blogging-misconceptions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2009 15:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/top-5-blogging-misconceptions/</guid>
      <description>If you promote it they might come. You could be writing the most fantastic blog on earth but if no one knows about it why bother? It’s almost like the old saying, “If a tree falls in the woods and no one is there to hear it, did it make a sound?
Unfortunately, we get bombarded all the time with unnecessary, irrelevant and useless products. But it proves the point: because of the promotion they thrive (not necessarily survive a long time or be considered a success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google SEM/SEO/SEA tools links</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/google-semseosea-tools-links/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2009 15:06:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/google-semseosea-tools-links/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7 tricks for your corporate twitter &amp;#8211; Turbomilk</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/7-tricks-for-your-corporate-twitter-turbomilk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2009 22:03:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/7-tricks-for-your-corporate-twitter-turbomilk/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Translations of the Spanish Manifesto in Defense of Fundamental Rights on the Internet</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/translations-of-the-spanish-manifesto-in-defe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2009 09:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/translations-of-the-spanish-manifesto-in-defe/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Howto watch, hear and use all those things you can&amp;#8217;t because of being abroad</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/howto-watch-hear-and-use-all-those-things-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2009 15:46:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/howto-watch-hear-and-use-all-those-things-you/</guid>
      <description>It sucks to be cut out to your culture because of your location. Internet, knowledge, arts, culture are universal and should be ubiquitous.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Investors: Venture Capitalists and Business Angels list in BetaGroup</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/investors-venture-capitalists-and-business-an/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2009 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/investors-venture-capitalists-and-business-an/</guid>
      <description>Among the services he provides to the community he has collected a very interesting selection of links to make the life of entrepreneurs easier, among which is this list of investors (venture capitalists and business angels). Check the **BetaGroup‘**s website for more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A journalist???s guide to SEO | Blog | Econsultancy</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/a-journalists-guide-to-seo-blog-econsultancy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2009 12:29:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/a-journalists-guide-to-seo-blog-econsultancy/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Study: Males vs. females in social networks | Royal Pingdom</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/study-males-vs-females-in-social-networks-roy-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2009 14:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/study-males-vs-females-in-social-networks-roy-4/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Webmission&amp;#8217;s family picture</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/the-webmissions-family-picture/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2009 13:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/the-webmissions-family-picture/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
