<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>funding on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/tags/funding/</link>
    <description>Recent content in funding on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2013 16:05:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.ramonsuarez.com/tags/funding/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How can market signals contribute to public startup funding?</title>
      <link>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/how-can-market-signals-contribute-to-public-s/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2013 16:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/how-can-market-signals-contribute-to-public-s/</guid>
      <description>One of the things that we discussed is how should to ensure that public funding on early stage startups does not bias the market, incentivising “good” ideas that nobody really cares about and ignoring others that are more needed.
My proposal, shared by other participants, is to follow market signals, so that it is the market that chooses and the public sector only reenforces those choices.
But the question is, which market signals?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Betagroup Presentation Template to Pitch to Investors</title>
      <link>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/betagroup-presentation-guidelines-to-pitch-to/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Feb 2011 15:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/betagroup-presentation-guidelines-to-pitch-to/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beta Group&amp;#8217;s Internet Entrepreneurship Links</title>
      <link>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/beta-groups-internet-entrepreneurship-links/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jun 2010 07:24:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/beta-groups-internet-entrepreneurship-links/</guid>
      <description>In case you do not know about it, the Beta Group is the largest Internet &amp;amp; Tech entrepreneurship networking event in Belgium, with about 350 attendees in each of its monthly meetups. The event consists of a pitch slam with six startups showcasing their products, short requests and announcements from the audience (the live tweets), and lots of networking over free warm beer. A must.
Disclosure: I am a member of the Beta Group’s council, and proud of it!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fred Destin&amp;#8217;s Workshop on Hacking Venture Capital</title>
      <link>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/fred-destins-workshop-on-hacking-venture-capi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2010 17:09:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/fred-destins-workshop-on-hacking-venture-capi/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three things you should never tell a VC when fundraising &amp;#8211; Fred Destin</title>
      <link>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/three-things-you-should-never-tell-a-vc-when/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2009 10:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/three-things-you-should-never-tell-a-vc-when/</guid>
      <description>Fred Destin is a VC I follow since I saw his brilliant participation in this roundtable at Plugg in Brussels: VC Panel: Where’s The Money Gone? from Plugg Conference on Vimeo.
He was completely detached at the beginning, but thanks to the arts of Matthäus Krzykowski he ended up getting fully into it and providing for one of the best moments of the conference.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Investors: Venture Capitalists and Business Angels list in BetaGroup</title>
      <link>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/investors-venture-capitalists-and-business-an/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2009 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/investors-venture-capitalists-and-business-an/</guid>
      <description>Among the services he provides to the community he has collected a very interesting selection of links to make the life of entrepreneurs easier, among which is this list of investors (venture capitalists and business angels). Check the **BetaGroup‘**s website for more.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
