<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>posterous on Ramon Suarez&#39;s curiosity lead learning life</title>
    <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/tags/posterous/</link>
    <description>Recent content in posterous on Ramon Suarez&#39;s curiosity lead learning life</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2009 11:00:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ramonsuarez.github.io/tags/posterous/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Huge visitors difference between Posterous stats and Google Analytics</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/huge-visitors-difference-between-posterous-st/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2009 11:00:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/huge-visitors-difference-between-posterous-st/</guid>
      <description>The more analytics I see, the more puzzled I am by the disparity among them. In this particular case, the huge difference between Posterous stats and Google Analytics after just one month of publishing.
According to Posterous, this blog has already received 1722 visits. But according to Google Analytics, it has received 294 with 499 page views, of which 222 are unique visitors. I guess that what Posterous counts are pageviews, but still the difference is way too big among them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bookmarklet link bug fixed in Posterous</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/bookmarklet-link-bug-fixed-in-posterous/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2009 11:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/bookmarklet-link-bug-fixed-in-posterous/</guid>
      <description>I had my first experiences with Posterous’ customer support this week and it has been very positive. As you can see from my posts, I use this blog as a notebook for content I find on the Internet (my memory in the cloud) thanks to Posterous’ wonderful bookmarklet. A few days ago, I went back to one of these “memories” and found that the links were not working (and that although it had over 100 readers, nobody had said a thing about it, but that’s another story).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
