<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>12 week year on Ramon Suarez&#39;s curiosity lead learning life</title>
    <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/tags/12-week-year/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 12 week year on Ramon Suarez&#39;s curiosity lead learning life</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2019 12:19:56 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ramonsuarez.github.io/tags/12-week-year/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>My First 12 Week Year in Review</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/my-first-12-week-year-in-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2019 12:19:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/my-first-12-week-year-in-review/</guid>
      <description>Since the launch of my first 12 week year a lot of things have happened and I’ve been able to continue churning out projects as part of my challenge.
12 Week Year One Results Projects The core of this three month year has been the projects and it has worked well. I’ve worked on other projects too (like the Target Shooting Journal), but the core of the challenge has been kept alive through:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My 12 Week Year Scorecard: Follow My Progress</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/my-12-week-year-scorecard-follow-my-progress-live/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 16:01:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/my-12-week-year-scorecard-follow-my-progress-live/</guid>
      <description>Part of the challenge of having goals and deadlines is tracking them and being able to see your project’s progress. To help me out I’m working on this scorecard that tracks the main goals and tactics of each 12 Week Year.
I’ve scoured the Internet for some templates to use and my scorecard is based on the spreadsheet created by Carrie Dils.
This is what the current scorecard looks like:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>12 Week Year Summary and Review</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/12-week-year-summary-and-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2019 11:46:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/12-week-year-summary-and-review/</guid>
      <description>The first of my book summary and review series has to be the book that has helped me to finally write down my vision and start a plan to move towards the future I want: The 12 Week Year: Get More Done in 12 Weeks than Others Do in 12 Months by Brian P. Moran and Michael Lennington.
The basic premise of the book is that yearly deadlines are way too long and that we tend to slack until the last minute, wasting too much time and having no time to maneuver left.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Life Goals and the Plan to Implement Them Using the 12 Week Year</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/my-vision-and-plan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2019 15:56:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/my-vision-and-plan/</guid>
      <description>One of the things that I want to improve through practice is structuring my work. Planning every week and day, keeping a productivity journal and using a task manager for all my projects has helped. I have advanced a lot in structuring and I’m now working to take it another step further with the implementation of a long term vision.
An important part of planning is prioritization, and for me this is intimately linked to your vision for the future.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
