<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Courses on Ramon Suarez&#39;s curiosity lead learning life</title>
    <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/categories/courses/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Courses on Ramon Suarez&#39;s curiosity lead learning life</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 15:54:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ramonsuarez.github.io/categories/courses/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Flop # 3: Coworking Course Post-Mortem</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/fail-3-coworking-course-post-mortem/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 15:54:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/fail-3-coworking-course-post-mortem/</guid>
      <description>After all the ins and outs of this course, only 4 people signed up. This is far from the target of 10 that I committed to in mastermind/accountability group. So I cancelled it, reimbursed everybody and closed my account in the e-learning platform (I don’t know if I will release it again nor when). In fact this puts on hold the other coworking courses I had in mind (marketing and sales).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ins and Outs of the  Coworking Course Launch</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/coworking-course-launched/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 15:19:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/coworking-course-launched/</guid>
      <description>It took a while, but the coworking community course has finally been launched. I kept my timing and the email announcing it went out last Thursday.
Doing a text only course was a good choice. It is much easier to work and rework the content and I can make the delivery much faster. The students have to put their time into doing the tasks to improve their own coworking space community, not on trying to understand my accent in a video.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Morphing: Online Text Course</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/project-morphing-online-text-course/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2019 12:32:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/project-morphing-online-text-course/</guid>
      <description>I’m not good with video yet, but there are many other delivery methods to share valuable content and help many people. So I’m going to continue working on the Coworking Community Course with a text only course.
The core of the course is ready, I have about 130 slides with a mix of information and exercises. It is a workbook focused on getting coworking space operators to take actions that will help them build a vibrant and healthy communities while they are taking the course and that will give provide a toolbox they can keep on using and referring to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting over Procrastination and Creator&amp;#8217;s Block</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/getting-over-procrastination-and-creators-block/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 15:16:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/getting-over-procrastination-and-creators-block/</guid>
      <description>Two things have contributed to this:
Creator’s block Self confidence Creator’s Block Making and online course is a creator challenge. Even if I’m using the content of my coworking book as the base, I’m adding a lot of content and I’m drafting it for video delivery.
I have a lot of experience writing, but not writing for video. Long gone are my days at Canal + in Spain where I was asked to do some writing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diving Deep into Online Course Making with Udemy</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/diving-deep-into-online-course-making-with-udemy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Nov 2018 11:30:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/diving-deep-into-online-course-making-with-udemy/</guid>
      <description>This week I’ve been really digging deep into Udemy’s help section for instructors. After finishing the outline for my Coworking Community course last week (I’m still looking for feedback).
I’ve finished all their video courses on how to create your content and how to record it and now I’m trying to get through with their Market Your Course 101 site. I’ve read a lot, and taken a lot of notes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update: Coworking Courses, Email Segmentation, Meditation Goals</title>
      <link>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/update-coworking-courses-email-segmentation-meditation-goals/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Nov 2018 11:38:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ramonsuarez.github.io/update-coworking-courses-email-segmentation-meditation-goals/</guid>
      <description>Coworking Courses This week I launched a poll to the members of The Coworking Handbook Newsletter asking them for their priorities for a coworking course: sales or community. The answer was a clear both, so I’ve started both of them.
To learn the ropes and get my hand dirtied I’ve chosen to go first with the coworking community course. It is much shorter than the sales course so it will be easier to finish and launch it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
