<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>communication on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/tags/communication/</link>
    <description>Recent content in communication on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2011 09:24:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.ramonsuarez.com/tags/communication/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Steve Rubel&amp;#8217;s Conference in Brussels: Audio &amp;#038; Notes</title>
      <link>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/steve-rubels-conference-in-brussels-audio-not/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2011 09:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/steve-rubels-conference-in-brussels-audio-not/</guid>
      <description>Audio: Steve Rubel’s Conference in Brussels There was an error in the way I was presented: I am the cofounder and manager of the Betagroup Coworking Brussels, together with the founder and CEO of the Betagroup: Jean Derely.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Choosing the Right Channel to Request Attention</title>
      <link>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/choosing-the-right-channel-to-request-attenti/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2011 09:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/choosing-the-right-channel-to-request-attenti/</guid>
      <description> The communication channnel choice is complex and does not depend on cost. The more attention it requires, the less people we interact with regularly. The two extremes of the table are Skype video conversations (3) and Facebook/Twitter broadcasting (100+) Cultural impact of availability on the choice of channel: the bussier the other person is, the less we will use a highly synchronous channel like phone or Skype. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 5 Blogging Misconceptions</title>
      <link>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/top-5-blogging-misconceptions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2009 15:07:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.ramonsuarez.com/top-5-blogging-misconceptions/</guid>
      <description>If you promote it they might come. You could be writing the most fantastic blog on earth but if no one knows about it why bother? It’s almost like the old saying, “If a tree falls in the woods and no one is there to hear it, did it make a sound?
Unfortunately, we get bombarded all the time with unnecessary, irrelevant and useless products. But it proves the point: because of the promotion they thrive (not necessarily survive a long time or be considered a success.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
